<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
  <title>NewsTracker: netanyahu</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://newstracker.github.io/timeline.netanyahu.xml" />
  <subtitle>This is a news tracking demo</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <title>Despite opposition to Iran deal, some Israelis fear Netanyahu has gone too far</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.startribune.com/on-nuclear-deal-not-all-israelis-are-with-netanyahu/322428141/" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-08-20T18:55:53Z</updated>
    <published>2015-08-20T18:55:53Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;In the seemingly unlikely event that Netanyahu prevails, many ask: What then?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Netanyahu loses, he will have gained nothing and potentially lost much by damaging the already strained relationship with the U.S., endangering a vital security alliance and American diplomatic cover at the United Nations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When it comes to the relationship between Israel and the United States, Netanyahu's problem is ... extreme courage, to the point of dangerousness," commentator Ari Shavit wrote in the Haaretz daily Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Instead of talking to the administration, Netanyahu is clashing with it," he wrote.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-08-20T18:55:53Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://stmedia.stimg.co/ows_144003579628076.jpg?h=150&amp;amp;amp;w=300&amp;amp;amp;fit=crop&amp;amp;amp;bg=999&amp;amp;amp;crop=faces" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Obama, Netanyahu make dueling appeals on Iran to US Jews</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.usnews.com/news/politics/articles/2015/08/04/obama-netanyahu-make-dueling-appeals-on-iran-to-us-jews" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-08-05T00:47:25Z</updated>
    <published>2015-08-05T00:47:25Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;"The nuclear deal with Iran doesn't block Iran's path to the bomb. It actually paves Iran's path to the bomb," Netanyahu said in his remarks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Netanyahu, one of the fiercest critics of the nuclear accord, also disputed Obama's assertion that opponents of the diplomatic deal favor war.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-08-05T00:47:25Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.usnews.com/dims4/USNEWS/c664701/2147483647/thumbnail/204x136%3E/quality/85/?url=%2Fcmsmedia%2F31%2F12%2Fefb873234c6f8055960f1f4360f0%2Fresizes%2F500%2Fthumb-3.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Carter, Netanyahu call it a day after discussing Iran deal</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2015/07/21/carter-netanyahu-call-it-a-day-after-discussing-iran-deal" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-21T18:45:14Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-21T18:45:14Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Carter on Tuesday did avoid a public tongue-lashing by Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Carter aide who attended the talks in Jerusalem later told reporters that Netanyahu bluntly expressed his opposition to the Iran deal but did not get angry or upset with Carter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. official said neither Carter nor Netanyahu raised the issue of potential U.S. compensation to Israel in the form of increased defense assistance to counter Iran-related threats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was the first Cabinet-level U.S. official to meet with Netanyahu since the signing of the Iran deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They shook hands and Netanyahu quickly steered Carter upstairs, to Carter's apparent surprise that Netanyahu was bypassing a chance to publicly attack the deal.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-21T18:45:14Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Carter, Netanyahu call it a day after discussing Iran deal</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Carter-Netanyahu-call-it-a-day-after-discussing-6397458.php" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-21T18:36:10Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-21T18:36:10Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Carter and Netanyahu met Tuesday in the prime minister's office in Jerusalem.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-21T18:36:10Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://ww3.hdnux.com/photos/37/64/16/8340382/3/square_gallery_thumb.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Israeli PM Benjamin Netanyahu faces criminal probe over spending</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.ctvnews.ca/world/israeli-pm-benjamin-netanyahu-faces-criminal-probe-over-spending-1.2479715" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-21T15:25:28Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-21T15:25:28Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;While the investigation shows no sign of threatening Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu's hold on power, it nonetheless gave him a new headache at a time of growing international isolation and domestic turmoil with a narrow and fractured coalition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Netanyahu and his wife, Sara, have for years faced scrutiny over their spending and have fended off accusations that their lifestyles are out of touch with regular Israelis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Justice Ministry declined to comment on what or who exactly would be investigated, but Israeli media said those charges, as well as another involving unusually high payments for Netanyahu's longtime electrician, would be at the centre of the probe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Netanyahu has faced a bumpy few months since being re-elected for a fourth term in March.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Under Netanyahu, Israel also has faced broadening international isolation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the biggest blow to Netanyahu was the signing last week of the international deal meant to curb Iran's nuclear program, which he had battled relentlessly and unsuccessfully to thwart.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-21T15:25:28Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Israel's Netanyahu struggles to govern with narrow majority</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.nzherald.co.nz/world/news/article.cfm?c_id=2&amp;amp;objectid=11484634&amp;amp;ref=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-21T07:45:22Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-21T07:45:22Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Netanyahu has also had to deal with scandals involving Likud backbenchers.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-21T07:45:22Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>After impressive election victory, Israel's Netanyahu struggles to govern with narrow majority</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.foxnews.com/world/2015/07/21/after-impressive-election-victory-israel-netanyahu-struggles-to-govern-with/?utm_source=feedburner&amp;amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+foxnews%2Fworld+%28Internal+-+World+Latest+-+Text%29" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-21T07:37:21Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-21T07:37:21Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ironically, Netanyahu's defeat over the Iran nuclear deal could work in his favor.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-21T07:37:21Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Israel's Netanyahu struggles to govern with narrow majority</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2015/07/21/israels-netanyahu-struggles-to-govern-with-narrow-majority" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-21T07:37:21Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-21T07:37:21Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;On course to become the longest serving prime minister in Israeli history, Netanyahu's legacy has not been marked so far by bold measures of war and peace that defined his predecessors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some would say that is just how Netanyahu likes it.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-21T07:37:21Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Israeli leader's household spending facing criminal probe</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.daytondailynews.com/ap/ap/international/israeli-leaders-household-spending-facing-criminal/nm33m/" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-21T06:45:45Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-21T06:45:45Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Israel's attorney general has ordered a criminal investigation into excessive spending at Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu's residences.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-21T06:45:45Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
</feed>
