<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
  <title>NewsTracker: tikrit</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://newstracker.github.io/timeline.tikrit.html" />
  <subtitle>This is a news tracking demo</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <title>No Iraq request for coalition air support in Tikrit campaign</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://news.yahoo.com/no-iraq-request-coalition-air-support-tikrit-campaign-122903962.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-19T21:34:15Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-19T21:34:15Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;A Pentagon spokesman said Iraqi forces essentially had Tikrit encircled but did not appear to have progressed as far in their operation to retake the city as initially suggested in early reporting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We have not been asked by the Iraqi government to conduct air strikes in Tikrit," said the senior military official in the coalition, declining to speculate why.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than 20,000 troops and Shi'ite militiamen are taking part in the offensive, which began more than two weeks ago, supported by a relatively small contingent of Sunni Muslim fighters from Tikrit and surrounding area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having made progress towards Tikrit, retaking surrounding towns before entering the city last week, the offensive slowed and there have been no major advances since Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S. Army Colonel Steve Warren, a Pentagon spokesman, said Iraqis initially had made statements indicating the fight to retake Tikrit was almost complete.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-19T21:34:15Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://l1.yimg.com/bt/api/res/1.2/3.PI5pdQKBE8RzjGE8zeoA--/YXBwaWQ9eW5ld3M7Zmk9ZmlsbDtoPTE5NjtxPTc1O3c9MzAw/http://media.zenfs.com/en_us/News/Reuters/2015-03-19T141548Z_1007000001_LYNXMPEB2I0PR_RTROPTP_2_CNEWS-US-MIDEAST-CRISIS-IRAQ-COALITION.JPG" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Mass grave uncovered in northern Iraqi city of Tikrit</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.ctvnews.ca/world/mass-grave-uncovered-in-northern-iraqi-city-of-tikrit-1.2287645" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-19T14:58:23Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-19T14:58:23Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Iraqi authorities in Salahuddin province unearthed 13 bodies in the district of al-Boajeel, east of the city of Tikrit, where security forces and Shiite militias are engaged in a large-scale offensive against the militants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iraqi troops backed by powerful Shiite militias are currently in a holding position on the edges of Tikrit as they wait for any remaining civilians to leave before pushing toward the centre of the city.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-19T14:58:23Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraq's Tikrit offensive stalled by IS bombs</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/afp/article-2998591/Iraqs-Tikrit-offensive-stalled-IS-bombs.html?ITO=1490&amp;ns_mchannel=rss&amp;ns_campaign=1490" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-17T15:06:09Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-17T15:06:09Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;"The battle to retake Tikrit will be difficult because of the preparations (IS) made," said Jawwad al-Etlebawi, spokesman for Asaib Ahl al-Haq, a Shiite militia playing a major role in the operation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They are made up largely of Shiite militiamen but some Sunni Arabs have also taken part in fighting in the Tikrit area, which is overwhelmingly Sunni Arab.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-17T15:06:09Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://i.dailymail.co.uk/i/pix/2015/03/17/article-doc-160e3-6X6Ab0PKu-HSK1-936_634x422.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Kurds report more chlorine attacks by Islamic State as Iraq pauses Tikrit offensive</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/worldnews/islamic-state/11476285/Kurds-report-more-chlorine-attacks-by-Islamic-State-as-Iraq-pauses-Tikrit-offensive.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-16T21:32:36Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-16T21:32:36Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Mohammed al-Ghaban, interior minister, said authorities had temporarily halted the offensive in Tikrit "to reduce casualties among our heroic forces... and to preserve the remaining infrastructure".&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-16T21:32:36Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://i.telegraph.co.uk/multimedia/archive/03234/Chlorine_gas_3234577b.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Saddam's tomb suffers extensive damage in fighting as Iraqi security forces battle for Tikrit</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.startribune.com/world/296375751.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-15T22:55:32Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-15T22:55:32Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;OUJA, Iraq - The tomb of Iraq's late dictator Saddam Hussein was virtually leveled in heavy clashes between militants from the Islamic State group and Iraqi forces in a fight for control of the city of Tikrit.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-15T22:55:32Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Saddam's tomb suffers extensive damage in clashes between Iraqi forces, ISIS</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.ctvnews.ca/world/saddam-s-tomb-suffers-extensive-damage-in-clashes-between-iraqi-forces-isis-1.2280877" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-15T21:08:00Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-15T21:08:00Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Fighting intensified to the north and south of Saddam Hussein's hometown Sunday as Iraqi security forces vowed to reach the centre of Tikrit within 48 hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Associated Press video from the village of Ouja, just south of Tikrit, shows all that remains of Hussein's once-lavish tomb are the support columns that held up the roof.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The extremist Islamic State group has controlled Tikrit since June, when it waged its lightning offensive that saw Iraq's second-largest city, Mosul, come under their control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recapturing Tikrit, a Sunni bastion on the Tigris River, would pave the way for an assault on Mosul, which U.S. officials have said could come as soon as next month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Concerns are mounting that Iraq's Shiite militias, of which an estimated 20,000 are fighting in Tikrit, will carry out revenge attacks on this and other areas that are home to predominantly Sunni residents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier this month, Human Rights Watch echoed those concerns, calling on the Iraqi government to protect civilians in Tikrit and allow them to flee combat zones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A satellite image of Tikrit, released last month by the United Nations, observed that at least 536 buildings in the city have been affected by the fighting, with at least 137 completely destroyed and 241 severely damaged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Local Sunni tribal fighters have formed uneasy alliances with the Iraqi army and Shiite militias in the battle for Tikrit, which Iraqi and U.S. officials believe is essential for defeating the Sunni militant group.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-15T21:08:00Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraqi offensive on Tikrit stalls, Kurds say Islamists used chlorine</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/03/15/us-mideast-crisis-iraq-idUSKBN0MB0MD20150315?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=worldNews" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-15T18:22:32Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-15T18:22:32Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;A military official returned from the front in Tikrit said no major advances were made by either side nearly two weeks into an operation to win back the city IS fighters seized last June.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We found a number of storage units containing chlorine that we think were seized by Daesh from water purification stations in different parts of Tikrit," Laith al-Jubouri said, using the Arabic acronym for the group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The military campaign to retake Tikrit has been stalled since Friday, when security officials said Iraqi forces and their militia allies would wait for reinforcements before moving forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There were no new pushes today from either side, only scattered skirmishes in the northern and southern parts of the city," Colonel Mohammed Abid al-Jubouri told Reuters by phone after visiting the southern edge of Tikrit on Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-15T18:22:32Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://s2.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&amp;d=20150315&amp;t=2&amp;i=1032592534&amp;w=580&amp;fh=&amp;fw=&amp;ll=&amp;pl=&amp;r=LYNXMPEB2E0BF" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraqi militia loyal to radical cleric joins Tikrit offensive</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/world/middle-east/Iraqi-militia-loyal-to-radical-cleric-joins-Tikrit-offensive/articleshow/46575539.cms" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-15T16:36:28Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-15T16:36:28Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;BAGHDAD: Dozens of fighters with the militia loyal to radical Shia cleric Muqtada al-Sadr left Iraq's capital on Sunday to take part in an offensive to capture Tikrit from the Islamic State group.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-15T16:36:28Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/thumb/msid-46575552,width-217,resizemode-4/Iraqi-militia-loyal-to-radical-cleric-joins-Tikrit-offensive.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraqi troops pause, await back-up in battle for Tikrit against militants</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/03/14/us-mideast-crisis-iraq-idUSKBN0MA0DX20150314?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=worldNews" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-14T16:04:25Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-14T16:04:25Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;More than 20,000 troops and Iranian-backed Shi'ite fighters entered Tikrit on Wednesday, having retaken areas to the north and south in Iraq's biggest offensive against the militants yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More "well-trained forces" were needed for the street-by-street battles that recapturing the city would require, the source said, speaking by phone from Tikrit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the army and Shi'ite militias, who are known as Hashid Shaabi (Popular Mobilisation), recaptured IS-held towns near Tikrit, a small number of residents who had fled the militants' advance began to return home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the outskirts of Samarra, a sacred Shi'ite city being used as a rear base for the Tikrit offensive further north, militants attacked an Iraqi army unit on Friday, two security officials said.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-14T16:04:25Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://s3.reutersmedia.net/resources_v2/images/masthead-logo.gif" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraqi troops pause battle for Tikrit, await reinforcements</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.globalpost.com/dispatch/news/regions/middle-east/iraq/150314/iraqi-troops-pause-battle-tikrit-await-reinforcements" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-14T15:18:41Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-14T15:18:41Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Military commanders had "reached a decision to halt the operation until a suitable, carefully set plan is in place" to break into central Tikrit, the source said.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-14T15:18:41Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.globalpost.com/sites/default/files/imagecache/gp3_small_article/photos/2015-March/iraq_tikrit_march_14_2015.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraqi forces pause in battle to drive Islamic State from Tikrit</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://news.yahoo.com/iraqi-offensive-dislodge-islamic-state-tikrit-appears-stall-123940204.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-13T23:13:48Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-13T23:13:48Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;A source in the military command said Iraqi forces would not move forward until reinforcements reached Tikrit, of which Islamic State still holds around half.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hadi al-Amiri, the head of the Shi'ite paramilitary Badr Organization and now one of the most powerful men in Iraq, said the outcome of the battle for Tikrit was in no doubt, but Iraqi forces needed time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iraqi special forces attacked a medical college in southern Tikrit at dawn, but the militants managed to fend them off, killing three soldiers, according to the military command source.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-13T23:13:48Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://l3.yimg.com/bt/api/res/1.2/v_VesSHTTtoiWPiXe6bCRQ--/YXBwaWQ9eW5ld3M7Zmk9ZmlsbDtoPTIwMDtxPTc1O3c9MzAw/http://media.zenfs.com/en_us/News/Reuters/2015-03-13T231348Z_2_LYNXMPEB2C0YL_RTROPTP_2_MIDEAST-CRISIS-IRAQ.JPG" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>An Iraqi offensive to dislodge the Islamic State from Tikrit seems to have stalled</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.globalpost.com/dispatch/news/regions/middle-east/iraq/150313/iraqi-offensive-dislodge-islamic-state-tikrit-seems-ha" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-13T16:12:00Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-13T16:12:00Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Islamic State fighters overran Tikrit last June during a lightning offensive that was halted just outside Baghdad.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-13T16:12:00Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.globalpost.com/sites/default/files/imagecache/gp3_small_article/photos/2015-March/iraqi-fighters-tikrit-2015-3-13.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>In Tikrit fight, Iraq Sunni preacher urges militia restraint</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.nzherald.co.nz/world/news/article.cfm?c_id=2&amp;objectid=11417077&amp;ref=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-13T12:00:27Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-13T12:00:27Z</published>
    <summary type="html" />
    <dc:date>2015-03-13T12:00:27Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraqi forces retake parts of Tikrit from the Islamic State</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.globalpost.com/dispatch/news/regions/middle-east/iraq/150311/iraqi-forces-retake-parts-tikrit-the-islamic-state" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-11T10:27:36Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-11T10:27:36Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;If Iraq's Shia-led government is able to retake Tikrit it would be the first city clawed back from the Sunni insurgents and would give it momentum in the next, pivotal stage of the campaign - to recapture Mosul, the largest city in the north.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-11T10:27:36Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.globalpost.com/sites/default/files/imagecache/gp3_small_article/photos/2015-March/tikrit-iraq-islamic-state-offensive.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraq seizes town on outskirts of Islamic State-held Tikrit</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.sfgate.com/world/article/Iraq-seizes-town-on-outskirts-of-Islamic-6126315.php" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-10T21:58:34Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-10T21:58:34Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Seizing Alam puts the offensive on course to attempt to liberate Tikrit in the coming days, the ultimate battle-readiness test for Iraqi forces now advancing there without the support of U.S.-led air strikes.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-10T21:58:34Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://ww4.hdnux.com/photos/35/10/00/7634963/3/square_gallery_thumb.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraqi troops, militia retake strategic town north of Tikrit from Islamic State</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/03/10/us-mideast-crisis-iraq-idUSKBN0M60UD20150310?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=worldNews" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-10T17:01:07Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-10T17:01:07Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;"We rejoice in this victory and we want al-Alam to be the launchpad for the liberation of Tikrit and Mosul," he told Reuters by telephone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Iraqi army and militias now control the two towns to the north and south of Tikrit along the Tigris river and appear ready to move on the city itself.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-10T17:01:07Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://s1.reutersmedia.net/resources/media/global/assets/images/20150310/20150310_5321685220150310173659.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Top US general optimistic about outcome of Tikrit battle</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2015/03/07/top-us-general-optimistic-about-outcome-of-tikrit-battle" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-07T14:46:51Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-07T14:46:51Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Its fighters swept across much of northern and western Iraq last summer and now control numerous key cities, including Tikrit, which is the birthplace of former Iraqi leader Saddam Hussein.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-07T14:46:51Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Top U.S. general optimistic about outcome of battle against ISIS in Iraqi city of Tikrit</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://news.nationalpost.com/2015/03/07/battle-of-tikrit/" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-07T14:38:45Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-07T14:38:45Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Army Gen. Martin Dempsey, chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff, was asked by reporters traveling with him from Washington to Iraq whether he believes ISIS fighters will be pushed out of Tikrit.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-07T14:38:45Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="https://nationalpostcom.files.wordpress.com/2015/03/464767732.jpg?w=620" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Top US general optimistic about outcome of Tikrit battle</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.nzherald.co.nz/world/news/article.cfm?c_id=2&amp;objectid=11413621&amp;ref=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-07T08:05:14Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-07T08:05:14Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Dempsey was asked by reporters traveling with him overnight Friday from Washington to Bahrain whether he believes IS will be pushed out of Tikrit.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-07T08:05:14Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://media.nzherald.co.nz/webcontent/image/jpg/201510/SCCZEN_AP150217050023_140x91.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Top US general optimistic about outcome of Tikrit battle</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://news.yahoo.com/top-us-general-optimistic-outcome-tikrit-battle-052414345--politics.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-07T06:56:15Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-07T06:56:15Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;"If it weren't for the (U.S.-led coalition) air campaign over time depleting the ISIL forces in Beiji ... then the current campaign (in Tikrit) as currently constructed would not be militarily feasible," he said.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-07T06:56:15Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://l.yimg.com/os/mit/media/m/base/images/transparent-649ba6f.png" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Top US general optimistic about outcome of Tikrit battle</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.sfgate.com/news/politics/article/Top-US-general-optimistic-about-outcome-of-Tikrit-6120444.php" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-07T06:56:10Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-07T06:56:10Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Iranian-backed Shiite militias and Sunni tribes have joined Iraq's military in a major operation to retake Tikrit from the Islamic State group, while the U.S. led coalition has remained on the sidelines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But in the Tikrit offensive, which began Monday, the U.S. is on the sidelines, watching as Iran asserts influence by providing training, weapons and leadership for Iraqi Shiite militias leading the charge on Tikrit.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-07T06:56:10Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://ww4.hdnux.com/photos/35/04/70/7622151/5/square_gallery_thumb.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State will be forced out of Tikrit, says top US general</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.theguardian.com/world/2015/mar/07/islamic-state-will-be-forced-out-of-tikrit-says-top-us-general" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-07T06:37:47Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-07T06:37:47Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The offensive is not what the Americans would consider textbook military tactics, he said, describing a hodge-podge of Iraqi Humvees, trucks and other vehicles surging toward Tikrit like "rush hour on the Washington Beltway".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The general said that while Iran is getting credit for enabling the Tikrit offensive, the full story of how it was made possible has not been told.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Isis forces had surged into Beyji, which lies just north of Tikrit, in hopes of controlling a key oil refinery there.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-07T06:37:47Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.theguardian.com//i.guim.co.uk/static/w-300/h--/q-95/sys-images/Guardian/Pix/pictures/2015/3/7/1425711053115/4e6d510a-0e0e-47c1-91bd-f4dd8d04d882-300x180.jpeg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraqi forces approach Tikrit as Islamic State destroys Nimrud</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.theage.com.au/world/iraqi-forces-approach-tikrit-as-islamic-state-destroys-nimrud-20150307-13xs3c.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-07T03:29:57Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-07T03:29:57Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Shiite fighters in Al Hadidiya, south of Tikrit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shiite militiamen and Iraqi troops entered the town of Dour, just south of Tikrit, on Friday, according to Iraqi state television.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-07T03:29:57Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.theage.com.au/content/dam/images/1/3/x/v/m/x/image.related.articleLeadNarrow.300x0.13xs3c.png/1425698979458.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Advancing Iraq troops enter strategic town on edge of Tikrit</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/03/06/us-mideast-crisis-iraq-idUSKBN0M21NS20150306?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=worldNews" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-06T15:46:11Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-06T15:46:11Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;But Hadi al-Amiri, leader of the largest Shi'ite militia group taking part in the operation, said al-Dour had been "totally liberated" and that the advance on another key town north of Tikrit, al-Alam, would take place on Saturday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The assault by the Shi'ite-led army and its militia allies on Tikrit in Iraq's Sunni heartland has symbolic importance for both sides.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials said on Friday they had captured a farm to the east of Tikrit that belonged to Saddam's deputy Ezzat Ibrahim al-Douri, now a prominent ally of the jihadist fighters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The United States, by contrast, says it has played no role in the Tikrit offensive despite an air campaign against Islamic State fighters in both Iraq and Syria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To the south of Tikrit, Islamic State militants attacked soldiers and militia fighters east of the city of Samarra with an explosives-laden tanker, killing four people and wounding 28, a source at Samarra hospital said.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-06T15:46:11Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraqi forces push toward Tikrit</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://edition.cnn.com/2015/03/04/middleeast/iraq-tikrit-battle/index.html?utm_source=feedburner&amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+rss%2Fedition_world+%28RSS%3A+World%29" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-06T13:40:31Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-06T13:40:31Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;"All commanders in Tikrit need to make sure that their forces protect civilians and allow them to flee the combat zone," said Joe Stork, the group's deputy Middle East and North Africa director.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-06T13:40:31Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://edition.cnn.com/2015/03/04/middleeast/iraq-tikrit-battle/data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhEAAJAJEAAAAAAP///////wAAACH5BAEAAAIALAAAAAAQAAkAAAIKlI+py+0Po5yUFQA7" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Fight for Iraqi city of Tikrit draws Tehran and Washington still closer together</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.theage.com.au/world/fight-for-iraqi-city-of-tikrit-draws-tehran-and-washington-still-closer-together-20150306-13x7l7.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-06T04:18:46Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-06T04:18:46Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;It's unclear how many Iranian troops are on the ground for the campaign to wrest control of Salaheddin province, and the strategic city of Tikrit, back from IS, but some are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A volunteer Shiite fighter prepares to join the battle against IS for control of the Iraqi city of Tikrit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A complaint by the Saudi Foreign Minister, Prince Saud al-Faisal, addressed the battle for Tikrit in particular - it was, he said, an indication of Iran's "hegemonic" tendencies.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-06T04:18:46Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.theage.com.au/content/dam/images/1/3/x/8/y/v/image.related.articleLeadNarrow.300x0.13x7l7.png/1425639994475.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State torches oil field near Tikrit as militia advance</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://news.yahoo.com/islamic-state-torches-oil-field-east-tikrit-witness-100124173.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-05T17:40:42Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-05T17:40:42Z</published>
    <summary type="html" />
    <dc:date>2015-03-05T17:40:42Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://l.yimg.com/bt/api/res/1.2/cWr5z5Ga_DSM_Xe1T46jUg--/YXBwaWQ9eW5ld3M7Zmk9ZmlsbDtoPTM3NztpbD1wbGFuZTtweG9mZj01MDtweW9mZj0wO3E9NzU7dz02NzA-/http://media.zenfs.com/en_us/News/Reuters/2015-03-05T104027Z_1948473891_GM1EB351FFL01_RTRMADP_3_MIDEAST-CRISIS-IRAQ.JPG" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State torches oil field east of Tikrit</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.smh.com.au/world/islamic-state-torches-oil-field-east-of-tikrit-20150305-13wl21.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-05T14:17:11Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-05T14:17:11Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Iraqi soldiers gather near their vehicles as smoke rises from oil wells in the Ajil field, east of the city of Tikrit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A police source in Salahuddin province, where Tikrit is located, said an eight-vehicle convoy of Islamic State insurgents attacked Iraqi forces at dawn on Thursday in al-Muaibidi, east of al-Alam.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-05T14:17:11Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.smh.com.au/content/dam/images/1/3/w/l/3/s/image.related.articleLeadwide.620x349.13wl21.png/1425565032139.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State torches oil field east of Tikrit</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.brisbanetimes.com.au/world/islamic-state-torches-oil-field-east-of-tikrit-20150305-13wl21.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-05T14:17:11Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-05T14:17:11Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Baghdad: Islamic State militants have set fire to oil wells north-east of the city of Tikrit to obstruct an assault by Shi'ite militia fighters and Iraqi soldiers trying to drive them from the area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Black smoke could be seen rising from the oil field since Wednesday afternoon, said the witness, who accompanied Iraqi militia and soldiers as they advanced on Tikrit from the east.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Soldiers and militia are also advancing along the Tigris river from the north and south of Tikrit, preparing for a joint offensive expected in coming days.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-05T14:17:11Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.brisbanetimes.com.au/content/dam/images/1/3/w/l/3/s/image.related.articleLeadwide.620x349.13wl21.png/1425565032139.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Concern grows for civilians as Iraq tightens noose on Tikrit</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/world/middle-east/Concern-grows-for-civilians-as-Iraq-tightens-noose-on-Tikrit/articleshow/46461842.cms" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-04T20:14:56Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-04T20:14:56Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;On Monday, around 30,000 Iraqi security forces and allied fighting units launched the biggest anti-IS ground operation yet in Iraq, closing in on Tikrit from at least three directions.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-04T20:14:56Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraq forces 'encircle IS in Tikrit'</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-middle-east-31727470#sa-ns_mchannel=rss&amp;ns_source=PublicRSS20-sa" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-04T13:13:41Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-04T13:13:41Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;A senior army commander said the operation was focused on preventing IS from launching more attacks, and cutting supply lines to stop reinforcements and weapons reaching Tikrit.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-04T13:13:41Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://news.bbcimg.co.uk/media/images/81364000/jpg/_81364464_tikrit_clashes_mar2015_624mapv2.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Snipers and booby traps slow Iraq forces from retaking Tikrit from Islamic State</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.theage.com.au/world/snipers-and-booby-traps-slow-iraq-forces-from-retaking-tikrit-from-islamic-state-20150303-13uaaa.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-03T17:34:44Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-03T17:34:44Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Baghdad: Iraqi forces have closed in on Tikrit, their progress slowed by jihadist snipers and booby traps, on the second day of Baghdad's largest operation yet against the Islamic State group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government has mobilised a 30,000-strong force for the push to retake Tikrit made up of Shiite militiamen and Sunni tribesmen as well as troops and police.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Outnumbered and outgunned, the jihadists who have held Tikrit since June 2014 have been resorting to guerrilla tactics to disrupt the government's three-pronged advance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iraqi forces are moving on Tikrit from three directions, with units targeting the towns of Al-Alam and Ad-Dawr to the north and south, while another large contingent drives on the city from the east.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-03T17:34:44Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.theage.com.au/content/dam/images/1/3/u/a/c/6/image.related.articleLeadwide.620x349.13uaaa.png/1425404075242.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraqi forces try to seal off Islamic State around Tikrit</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://news.yahoo.com/iraqi-forces-try-seal-off-islamic-state-around-110400440.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-03T11:04:00Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-03T11:04:00Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;In contrast, the U.S.-led air coalition which has been attacking Islamic State across Iraq and Syria has not played a role in Tikrit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They have yet to enter Tikrit, the hometown of executed former president Saddam Hussein, or the nearby Tigris river town of al-Dour, which officials describe as a major center for the Islamic State fighters.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-03T11:04:00Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://l.yimg.com/os/mit/media/m/base/images/transparent-649ba6f.png" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Fierce clashes outside Iraq's Tikrit after new offensive</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://hosted2.ap.org/APDEFAULT/cae69a7523db45408eeb2b3a98c0c9c5/Article_2015-03-03-ML--Islamic%20State/id-609eee993a4a40c19e1e79f671b59223" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-03T09:56:41Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-03T09:56:41Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;They say government forces backed by Shiite militias and Sunni tribal fighters have made little progress on the second day of a large-scale military operation to recapture Tikrit, which fell to the Islamic State group last summer.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-03T09:56:41Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraq launches operation to retake Tikrit from Islamic State</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://news.yahoo.com/iraq-state-tv-operation-retake-tikrit-begins-065057934.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-02T20:33:07Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-02T20:33:07Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;"Right now we are not providing any air power to support the Iraqi operation in the city of Tikrit," Warren told reporters in Washington.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-02T20:33:07Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://l.yimg.com/os/mit/media/m/base/images/transparent-649ba6f.png" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraq launches assault to retake Tikrit</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.sbs.com.au/news/article/2015/03/03/iraq-launches-assault-retake-tikrit-0" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-02T20:13:03Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-02T20:13:03Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The video describes those executed as belonging to a tribal group named after a town just north of Tikrit.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-02T20:13:03Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.sbs.com.au/news/sites/sbs.com.au.news/files/styles/thumb_small/public/20150303001107697814-original.jpg?itok=nLae4mla" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>ISIS executes four Iraqis from Tikrit</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.sbs.com.au/news/article/2015/03/03/iraq-launches-assault-retake-tikrit-0" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-02T19:11:05Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-02T19:11:05Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Government forces have battled their way north for months, notching up key victories against IS, but Tikrit has been their toughest target yet with the jihadists having resisted them several times.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-02T19:11:05Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.sbs.com.au/news/sites/sbs.com.au.news/files/styles/thumb_small/public/20150303001107697814-original.jpg?itok=nLae4mla" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraq launches major offensive to retake Tikrit from Islamic State</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.smh.com.au/world/iraq-launches-major-offensive-to-retake-tikrit-from-islamic-state-20150303-13t6xt.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-02T17:37:56Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-02T17:37:56Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;So far local reports indicated the army, backed by as many as 27,000 soldiers as well as Iraqi fighter jets and helicopters, had attacked the city from three sides but had yet to make it inside Tikrit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Along with opening up a key supply route for any future military operation to take back Mosul from IS, the campaign in Tikrit will show the measure of the Iraqi Army, which suffered a humiliating defeat last June when thousands of its soldiers abandoned their posts to IS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This operation [in Tikrit] therefore likely has major support from Iraq's Shiite communities, which bore the brunt of these losses . . . and are therefore highly motivated to deal a counterblow in this symbolic area," the Washington-based Institute for the Study of War said.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-02T17:37:56Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.smh.com.au/content/dam/images/1/3/t/6/z/f/image.related.articleLeadwide.620x349.13t6xt.png/1425351396605.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraq launches major offensive to retake Tikrit from Islamic State</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.brisbanetimes.com.au/world/iraq-launches-major-offensive-to-retake-tikrit-from-islamic-state-20150303-13t6xt.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-02T17:37:56Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-02T17:37:56Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;There are also deep concerns that civilians will get caught in the crossfire, with the UN Secretary-General's special representative for Iraq, Nickolay Mladenov, urging all armed forces in Tikrit to ensure the safety of civilians.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tikrit was the scene of one of the first and largest massacres conducted by IS, when it kidnapped and murdered hundreds of Iraqi security forces from the nearby military base of Camp Speicher.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-02T17:37:56Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.brisbanetimes.com.au/content/dam/images/1/3/t/6/z/f/image.related.articleLeadwide.620x349.13t6xt.png/1425351396605.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Pentagon: US not providing air support for Iraqi offensive</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://news.yahoo.com/pentagon-us-not-providing-air-support-iraqi-offensive-171225459.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-02T17:12:25Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-02T17:12:25Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Warren said he could not comment on any Iranian military involvement, beyond saying Washington is aware of Iran's interest in Iraq's fight against the Islamic State group that controls key territory, including Tikrit and Mosul.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-02T17:12:25Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Pentagon says no US air power supporting Iraqi offensive in Tikrit; Iraqis did not ask</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.startribune.com/nation/294680571.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-02T17:10:55Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-02T17:10:55Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Warren said he could not provide an assessment of Iraqi progress in the Tikrit battle.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-02T17:10:55Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraq launches major assault to retake Tikrit from Islamic State</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://news.yahoo.com/major-offensive-under-way-retake-iraqs-tikrit-army-081036649.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-02T16:27:54Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-02T16:27:54Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Iraqi forces have tried and failed several times to wrest back Tikrit, a Sunni Arab city on the Tigris river about 160 kilometres (100 miles) north of Baghdad.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-02T16:27:54Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://l.yimg.com/os/mit/media/m/base/images/transparent-649ba6f.png" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraq's Tikrit: A Sunni bastion on the road to Mosul</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://hosted2.ap.org/APDEFAULT/cae69a7523db45408eeb2b3a98c0c9c5/Article_2015-03-02-ML--Islamic%20State-Tikrit-Glance/id-ba7d52ee975d4483a3e589a853243a60" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-02T15:56:28Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-02T15:56:28Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The hometown of Saddam Hussein, Tikrit is on the main highway from Baghdad to Mosul, Iraq's second largest city, which is also held by the Islamic State.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-02T15:56:28Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraq launches operation to retake Tikrit from Islamic State</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://hosted2.ap.org/APDEFAULT/cae69a7523db45408eeb2b3a98c0c9c5/Article_2015-03-02-ML--Islamic%20State/id-d8599a03e0994ff1b0d1ff90ba63b827" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-02T15:56:28Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-02T15:56:28Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;FILE - In this Sunday, April 13, 2003 file photo, a statue of Iraqi President Saddam Hussein is seen as the streets are nearly deserted in central Tikrit, Iraq.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-02T15:56:28Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraq launches operation to retake Tikrit from Islamic State</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2015/03/02/iraq-state-tv-operation-to-retake-tikrit-begins" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-02T13:47:56Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-02T13:47:56Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Previous attempts to capture the symbolic city have failed, and hours into Monday's operation, the military said it still hadn't entered Tikrit, indicating a long battle lies ahead.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-02T13:47:56Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraq launches operation to retake Tikrit from Islamic State</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.sfgate.com/news/world/article/Iraq-state-TV-Operation-to-retake-Tikrit-begins-6109425.php" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-02T13:47:56Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-02T13:47:56Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Tikrit, the provincial capital of Salauhddin province, 80 miles (130 kilometers) north of Baghdad, fell to the Islamic State group last summer, along with Mosul and other areas in the country's Sunni heartland.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-02T13:47:56Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://ww4.hdnux.com/photos/30/53/25/6468935/7/square_gallery_thumb.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraq third large-scale military operation to recapture Tikrit from ISIS faces major opposition</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://news.nationalpost.com/2015/03/02/iraq-launches-large-scale-military-operation-to-recapture-tikrit-from-isis/" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-02T13:33:31Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-02T13:33:31Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;But hours into the operation, a key test for the embattled Iraqi army, the military said it still hadn't entered the city of Tikrit, indicating a long battle lies ahead.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-02T13:33:31Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="https://nationalpostcom.files.wordpress.com/2015/03/538457338.jpg?w=620" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraq launches operation to retake Tikrit from ISIS</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.cbc.ca/news/world/iraq-launches-operation-to-retake-tikrit-from-isis-1.2978011?cmp=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-02T10:51:30Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-02T10:51:30Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;State-run Al-Iraqiya television said that forces were attacking Tikrit from different directions, backed by artillery and airstrikes by Iraqi fighter jets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S.-led coalition launching airstrikes targeting ISIS were not involved in the Tikrit operation, Iraqi officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Past attempts to retake Tikrit have failed, however, as Iraq struggles with its armed forces, which collapsed in the wake of the ISIS's offensive last summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fars also reported drones were flying over Tikrit, without identifying whether the drones were Iranian or Iraqi.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-02T10:51:30Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Iraqi forces move on Tikrit: TV report</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.theage.com.au//breaking-news-world/iraqi-forces-move-on-tikrit-tv-report-20150302-3ray7.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-02T07:13:09Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-02T07:13:09Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Tikrit, about 130 kilometres north of Baghdad, fell into the hands of IS last northern summer along with the country's second-largest city of Mosul and other areas in the Sunni heartland.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-02T07:13:09Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
</feed>
