<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <title>NewsTracker: van morrison</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://newstracker.github.io/timeline.van_morrison.rss" />
  <subtitle>This is a news tracking demo</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <title>Van Morrison on 'Re-Working the Catalogue' with an all-star lineup</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.charlotteobserver.com/entertainment/music-news-reviews/article16170860.html%23storylink=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-24T15:17:04Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-24T15:17:04Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;That number increased with Monday's release of Morrison's new album, "Duets: Re-Working the Catalogue."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Morrison, "There were two parts to it," the 69-year-old artist told The Times in an exclusive email interview.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morrison has spent the vast majority of his career looking ahead, writing and recording a string of studio albums that now numbers more than three dozen; "Duets: Re-Working the Catalogue" represents a rare dip into his past.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During that event, Morrison invited Staples, Womack and Cole to go into a recording studio to get the ball rolling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I first heard him in the '60s at a show with Aretha Franklin and Dr. John and I thought then, 'Who is this guy?'" Mahal told The Times at a performance Morrison gave last summer outside his hometown of Belfast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What I love about Van so much was that you couldn't categorize him," said Buble, who sings one of his favorite Morrison songs, "Real Real Gone," on the album.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morrison's storied back catalog, which stretches back to his recordings with the Irish rock band Them in 1965, encompasses hundreds of songs that he and his duet partners drew from for the new album.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-24T15:17:04Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Review: Van Morrison breaks mold in diverse duets album</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.nzherald.co.nz/entertainment/news/article.cfm?c_id=1501119&amp;amp;objectid=11421979&amp;amp;ref=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-23T16:55:14Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-23T16:55:14Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Their easy camaraderie makes one miss the late John Lee Hooker, who teamed with Morrison for some of the finest duets of their respective careers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chris Farlowe, who has joined Morrison on stage at times, teams up with him on "Born To Sing" and former bandmate Georgie Fame duets on "Get On With the Show."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There's plenty to hear, and there's plenty more hidden away in Morrison's impressive archives.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-23T16:55:14Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
</feed>
