<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
  <title>NewsTracker: tsipras</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://newstracker.github.io/timeline.tsipras.xml" />
  <subtitle>This is a news tracking demo</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <title>Tsipras sees Greek deal, but differences remain after EU talks</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/reuters/article-3110347/Tsipras-sees-Greek-deal-differences-remain-EU-talks.html?ITO=1490&amp;amp;ns_mchannel=rss&amp;amp;ns_campaign=1490" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-04T03:01:57Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-04T03:01:57Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;But as Tsipras's party battles to retain support from voters who elected in January to end years of austerity, its spokesman in parliament renewed tough rhetoric at home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tsipras, whose government has been critical of a hard line from the IMF, again praised Juncker's executive for showing understanding of the Greek predicament.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-04T03:01:57Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Tsipras sees Greek deal, but differences remain after EU talks</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/06/04/us-eurozone-greece-idUSKBN0OK05820150604?feedType=RSS&amp;amp;feedName=businessNews" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-04T02:04:03Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-04T02:04:03Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Greek Prime Minister Alexis Tsipras (L) poses with European Commission President Jean-Claude Juncker ahead of a meeting at the EU Commission headquarters in Brussels, Belgium, June 3, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, Tsipras has produced a plan of his own and said he intended to discuss that document in Brussels, calling on euro zone partners to show some "realism" and urging a deal that would let Greece escape from "economic asphyxiation".&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-04T02:04:03Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Tsipras sees Greek deal, but differences remain after EU talks</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsipras-sees-greek-deal-differences-020403267.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-04T02:04:03Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-04T02:04:03Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;"At the end of the day," Tsipras said, "I think the proposals on the table will be the proposals of the Greek government."&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-04T02:04:03Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://l.yimg.com/bt/api/res/1.2/7e.3f4heTRiPVYDgfQc_zg--/YXBwaWQ9eW5ld3M7Zmk9ZmlsbDtoPTM3NztpbD1wbGFuZTtweG9mZj01MDtweW9mZj0wO3E9NzU7dz02NzA-/http://globalfinance.zenfs.com/images/US_AHTTP_REUTERS_OLUSBUS_WRAPPER_H_LIVE_NEW/2015-06-04T020403Z_1_LYNXMPEB5301Z_RTROPTP_3_EUROZONE-GREECE_original.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Greek leader heads to Brussels to defend deal proposal</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/business/national-business/article22980480.html%23storylink=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-03T15:12:07Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-03T15:12:07Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ahead of his meeting with Commission head Jean-Claude Juncker, Alexis Tsipras stressed the need for compromise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I will go to ... explain to him that today more than ever it is necessary for the (creditor) institutions and mainly for the political leadership of Europe to sign up to realism," Tsipras said before leaving for Brussels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speaking before leaving for Brussels, Tsipras said he had not yet received any document.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tsipras says he submitted his proposal to creditors on Monday night but gave no details of what fiscal reforms Greece was suggesting in return for its final bailout funds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elected in January on promises to repeal the deeply resented austerity measures Greece had to impose in return for its five-year bailout, Tsipras said his government had made concessions during the negotiations.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-03T15:12:07Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.charlotteobserver.com/static/img/placeholder/FREE.gif" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Greek PM heads to Brussels to present latest deal proposal</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.sfgate.com/news/world/article/Greek-PM-heads-to-Brussels-to-present-latest-deal-6303336.php" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-03T06:43:19Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-03T06:43:19Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Greece's Prime Minister Alexis Tsipras leads a meeting at the Education Ministry in Athens, Tuesday, June 2, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-03T06:43:19Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Greek PM heads to Brussels to present latest deal proposal</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.usnews.com/news/business/articles/2015/06/03/greek-pm-heads-to-brussels-to-present-latest-deal-proposal" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-03T06:43:19Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-03T06:43:19Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Tsipras says Greece has submitted a proposal for an agreement with its creditors, as Athens seeks a deal that will to unlock desperately needed rescue money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tsipras was invited to Brussels by European Commission head Jean Claude Juncker, with whom he was to meet for talks Wednesday evening, a Greek government official said.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-03T06:43:19Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Uncertainty shrouds Greek debt talks after Tsipras tirade</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.dailymail.co.uk/wires/reuters/article-3106213/Uncertainty-shrouds-Greek-debt-talks-Tsipras-tirade.html?ITO=1490&amp;amp;ns_mchannel=rss&amp;amp;ns_campaign=1490" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-01T18:02:23Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-01T18:02:23Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;In an article in the French daily Le Monde which European diplomats said appeared intended to show Greek voters how hard he was fighting, Tsipras accused the lenders of making "absurd proposals" and disregarding Greek democracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Referring to creditors' demands for further pension cuts and rejection of restoring collective wage bargaining, Tsipras said they amounted to "the complete abolition of democracy in Europe" and the creation of a "technocratic monstrosity".&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-01T18:02:23Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Greece's Tsipras Insists "Very Close" to Deal With Lenders</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/greeces-tsipras-close-deal-lenders-31078068" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-05-15T20:45:46Z</updated>
    <published>2015-05-15T20:45:46Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Speaking an annual financial conference in Athens, Tsipras said the government had not abandoned its goal to try and persuade lenders to restructure Greece's debt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It appears that we have reached common ground with the institutions on a number of issues, and that makes us optimistic that we are really very close to an agreement," Tsipras said, noting convergence on harmonized sales tax rates and tax administration reforms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 40-year-old Tsipras won January elections promising undo austerity measures that stabilized public finances but cause a massive drop in output, triggering a wave of poverty and unemployment.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-05-15T20:45:46Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Greece's Tsipras says "very close" to deal with lenders</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.usnews.com/news/business/articles/2015/05/15/greeces-tsipras-says-very-close-to-deal-with-lenders" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-05-15T19:31:14Z</updated>
    <published>2015-05-15T19:31:14Z</published>
    <summary type="html" />
    <dc:date>2015-05-15T19:31:14Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Tsipras presses for early Greek debt deal but flags referendum</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/04/28/us-eurozone-greece-idUSKBN0NJ0FT20150428?feedType=RSS&amp;amp;feedName=worldNews" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-04-28T07:45:11Z</updated>
    <published>2015-04-28T07:45:11Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;But Tsipras also said he would have to resort to a referendum if lenders insisted on demands deemed unacceptable by his leftist government, elected to scrap austerity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pressed on the options if no deal were found, Tsipras ruled out snap elections but said the government did not have the right to accept demands that fell outside the limits of its mandate and would have to ask Greeks to decide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The moves effectively took the talks out of the hands of Varoufakis, although Tsipras defended the flamboyant intellectual, while acknowledging that the mood towards Greece among euro zone finance ministers was sour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tsipras accused the previous conservative-led Greek government and unnamed forces in Europe of laying a "trap" for his government when it took power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They derive pleasure from the prospect of a failure in the talks," Tsipras said, saying his government had walked into a "minefield" when it took office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ECB barred banks from posting Greek government bonds as collateral to obtain funds in its regular monetary tenders in February, since Tsipras' government had vowed not to complete its international bailout program.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In another jibe against European partners, Tsipras said his government made a mistake by accepting a verbal rather than written commitment that the ECB decision would be reversed once Greece got a deal to extend its bailout.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-04-28T07:45:11Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Greek Prime Minister Tsipras Rules out Early Elections If Bailout Talks With Creditors Fail</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/greek-prime-minister-tsipras-rules-early-elections-bailout-30625875" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-04-27T21:56:43Z</updated>
    <published>2015-04-27T21:56:43Z</published>
    <summary type="html" />
    <dc:date>2015-04-27T21:56:43Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Merkel to press Greece's Tsipras for progress on reforms</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/04/23/us-eurozone-greece-idUSKBN0NE1CP20150423?feedType=RSS&amp;amp;feedName=businessNews" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-04-23T12:26:44Z</updated>
    <published>2015-04-23T12:26:44Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;"At the highest level, the Germans want to keep Greece in the euro area and find a solution, but time is running short and there may have to be more drama before Tsipras can put his foot down and reach an agreement," one senior official said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Greek government official told Reuters in Athens that Tsipras would outline specific reforms to Merkel in a bid to appease creditors and is hoping she will intervene so that there is a breakthrough in the negotiations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tsipras, elected in January on an anti-austerity platform, is resisting cutting pensions, liberalizing the labor market or raising value-added tax on Greek holiday islands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tsipras' office said he would also have a private meeting with French President Francois Hollande on the summit sidelines.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-04-23T12:26:44Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Putin gives visiting Greek PM Tsipras historic Greek icon</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://news.yahoo.com/putin-gives-visiting-greek-pm-tsipras-ancient-greek-094938369.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-04-09T13:13:22Z</updated>
    <published>2015-04-09T13:13:22Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Putin's spokesman Dmitry Peskov said Putin presented the icon depicting St. Nicholas and St. Spyridon to Tsipras following Wednesday's talks at the Kremlin.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-04-09T13:13:22Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://l.yimg.com/bt/api/res/1.2/9OG46j7Sl36xv6jdHyJ9lA--/YXBwaWQ9eW5ld3M7Zmk9ZmlsbDtoPTM3NztpbD1wbGFuZTtweG9mZj01MDtweW9mZj0wO3E9NzU7dz02NzA-/http://media.zenfs.com/en_us/News/ap_webfeeds/a23f0436f1142b0f730f6a706700f236.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Putin gives visiting Greek prime minister Tsipras an ancient Greek icon once stolen by Nazis</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.foxnews.com/world/2015/04/09/putin-gives-visiting-greek-prime-minister-tsipras-ancient-greek-icon-once/?utm_source=feedburner&amp;amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+foxnews%2Fworld+%28Internal+-+World+Latest+-+Text%29" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-04-09T11:47:28Z</updated>
    <published>2015-04-09T11:47:28Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Speaking Thursday, Tsipras reaffirmed his opposition to Western sanctions slapped on Russia last year and said his government helped block proposals to strengthen the sanctions.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-04-09T11:47:28Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Putin gives visiting Greek PM Tsipras ancient Greek icon</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.sfgate.com/news/world/article/Putin-gives-visiting-Greek-PM-Tsipras-ancient-6188719.php" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-04-09T11:47:28Z</updated>
    <published>2015-04-09T11:47:28Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Sergei Naryshkin, right, speaker of the State Duma, lower parliament chamber, right, welcomes Greek Prime Minister Alexis Tsipras in Moscow, Russia, Thursday, April 9, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Greece's international creditors are watching Tsipras' visit to Russia with concern amid speculation that Greece might seek aid from Russia, as a bargaining chip with Western creditors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speaking to students, Tsipras said he and Putin have found a way to resume Greek agricultural exports, which were blocked last year under Russia's ban on Western food in retaliation to the EU sanctions.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-04-09T11:47:28Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://ww3.hdnux.com/photos/35/55/66/7789954/5/square_gallery_thumb.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Putin meets with Greece's Tsipras</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.upi.com/Top_News/World-News/2015/04/08/Putin-meets-with-Greeces-Tsipras/4151428508928/" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-04-08T16:28:07Z</updated>
    <published>2015-04-08T16:28:07Z</published>
    <summary type="html" />
    <dc:date>2015-04-08T16:28:07Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Tsipras and Putin agree closer ties at Moscow talks</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.dw.de/tsipras-and-putin-agree-closer-ties-at-moscow-talks/a-18367626?maca=en-rss-en-world-4025-rdf" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-04-08T14:43:00Z</updated>
    <published>2015-04-08T14:43:00Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The EU Parliament's president has warned Tsipras not to break the line on EU sanctions towards Russia.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-04-08T14:43:00Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.dw.de/image/0,,18367549_303,00.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Greek PM Tsipras in Moscow for talks</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-32213161%23sa-ns_mchannel=rss&amp;amp;ns_source=PublicRSS20-sa" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-04-08T12:39:21Z</updated>
    <published>2015-04-08T12:39:21Z</published>
    <summary type="html" />
    <dc:date>2015-04-08T12:39:21Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/200/media/images/82175000/jpg/_82175150_026646980-1.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Tsipras heads to Moscow, Europeans keeping wary eye on visit</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.nzherald.co.nz/world/news/article.cfm?c_id=2&amp;amp;objectid=11429227&amp;amp;ref=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-04-07T16:50:11Z</updated>
    <published>2015-04-07T16:50:11Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Alexis Tsipras' government " a coalition of the radical left and nationalist right elected in January on promises to repeal the austerity measures imposed as a condition of the rescue " has been flirting with Moscow from the start.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moscow hopes talks with Tsipras will help further weaken the EU's resolve to maintain the sanctions against Russia, said Sergei Oznobishchev, head of Russia's independent Institute of Strategic Assessment.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-04-07T16:50:11Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Tsipras heads to Moscow, Europeans keeping wary eye on visit</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.nzherald.co.nz/business/news/article.cfm?c_id=3&amp;amp;objectid=11429227&amp;amp;ref=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-04-07T16:50:11Z</updated>
    <published>2015-04-07T16:50:11Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Tough talk, particularly in relation to Greece's creditors, has made Tsipras' popularity soar at home, with many Greeks saying they have regained a sense of lost national pride.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But analysts warn Tsipras is playing a dangerous game, particularly if the tough talk reflects actual intentions rather than just rhetoric aimed at a domestic audience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tsipras has made no secret of his disagreement with the EU's position on Russia.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-04-07T16:50:11Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://media.nzherald.co.nz/webcontent/image/jpg/201513/SCCZEN_AP150320140900_140x93.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Greece disagrees with sanctions against Russia, Tsipras says</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.miamiherald.com/news/business/article17006621.html%23storylink=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-31T18:49:04Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-31T18:49:04Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;"We do not agree with sanctions. I believe that this is a road to nowhere. I support the point of view that there is a need for a dialogue and diplomacy," Tsipras added.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-31T18:49:04Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Greece disagrees with sanctions against Russia, Tsipras says</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/business/national-business/article17006621.html%23storylink=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-31T18:49:04Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-31T18:49:04Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Greece's new government disagrees with sanctions against Russia, and wants to boost trade ties with the country, Prime Minister Alexis Tsipras said before a visit to Moscow next week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;France and Germany on Tuesday downplayed Tsipras' upcoming visit to Moscow, where he will meet with Russian President Vladimir Putin on April 8.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-31T18:49:04Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Merkel and Tsipras meet, but little sign of debt progress</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://america.aljazeera.com/articles/2015/3/23/merkel-tsipras-display-goodwill-but-few-signs-debt-progress.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-23T23:10:00Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-23T23:10:00Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Tsipras said Merkel invited him to Berlin for talks as the tensions between the two countries increased, telling him "it is better to talk with one another than about one another."&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-23T23:10:00Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://america.aljazeera.com/content/ajam/articles/2015/3/22/tsipras-merkel-to-meet-over-greek-debt/_jcr_content/image.adapt.480.low.Greece_Germany_032215.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Tsipras, Merkel urge end to name-calling</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.sbs.com.au/news/article/2015/03/24/tsipras-merkel-urge-end-name-calling" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-23T20:42:37Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-23T20:42:37Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Tsipras said the budget cuts and structural reforms demanded over the last five years in exchange for two bailout programmes had not been a "success story" but rather brought his country to its knees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As tensions have flared, painful historical memories have resurfaced, with Tsipras's government reviving reparation claims for the Nazi occupation of Greece in World War II.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In his opening statement, Tsipras stressed that Greece did not see the case as closed, insisting that it was a "moral issue" that must still be resolved.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-23T20:42:37Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.sbs.com.au/news/sites/sbs.com.au.news/files/styles/thumb_small/public/images/2/6/26Feb_AngelaMerkel_800x600.jpg?itok=IrwYu7LG" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>A glance at issues that divide Germany and Greece as new PM Tsipras makes 1st visit to Berlin</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.startribune.com/world/297233561.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-23T13:20:22Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-23T13:20:22Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;BERLIN - Relations between Greece's new government and Germany got off to a rocky start after Prime Minister Alexis Tsipras swept to power in January on pledges to end the budget austerity Germany had been pushing for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are some of the issues causing friction as Tsipras makes his first visit to Berlin to meet Chancellor Angela Merkel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tsipras' left-wing party argues that austerity has been counterproductive but agreed a month ago to push through reforms in exchange for keeping European Union aid flowing.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-23T13:20:22Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Greek debt &amp;#039;impossible&amp;#039; to repay: Tsipras</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.sbs.com.au/news/article/2015/03/23/greek-debt-impossible-repay-tsipras" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-23T12:16:23Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-23T12:16:23Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Tsipras is to meet Merkel in Berlin later on Monday.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-23T12:16:23Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Tsipras on first trip to Germany amid tense relations</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://finance.yahoo.com/news/tsipras-first-trip-germany-amid-073017678.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-23T11:10:53Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-23T11:10:53Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Tsipras' party won general elections in January after campaigning against the spending cuts favored by Germany in exchange for 240 billion euros ($260 billion) in international bailout money.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-23T11:10:53Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://l.yimg.com/bt/api/res/1.2/FBCqecAuNXYWKsIsCkzF7Q--/YXBwaWQ9eW5ld3M7Zmk9ZmlsbDtoPTM3NztpbD1wbGFuZTtweG9mZj01MDtweW9mZj0wO3E9NzU7dz02NzA-/http://globalfinance.zenfs.com/images/US_AHTTP_AP_HEADLINES_BUSINESS/d925c1333478920d710f6a7067001d05_original.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Tsipras on first trip to Germany amid tense relations</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.nzherald.co.nz/business/news/article.cfm?c_id=3&amp;amp;objectid=11421845&amp;amp;ref=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-23T08:35:17Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-23T08:35:17Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;"I did not come here to ask for financial help," Tsipras told reporters after meeting with Merkel behind closed doors for more than an hour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Merkel was careful to point out Germany was only one of the eurozone nations that would be responsible for deciding whether Greece's reforms are sufficient, and said no decisions had been made in her talks with Tsipras.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-23T08:35:17Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Tsipras on first trip to Germany amid tense relations</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.foxbusiness.com/markets/2015/03/23/tsipras-visits-germany-for-first-time-as-greek-leader-as-countries-seek-to-mend/?utm_source=feedburner&amp;amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+foxbusiness%2Fmarkets+%28Internal+-+Markets+-+Text%29" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-23T07:30:08Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-23T07:30:08Z</published>
    <summary type="html" />
    <dc:date>2015-03-23T07:30:08Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Tsipras visits Germany for first time as Greek leader as countries seek to mend relations</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.foxbusiness.com/markets/2015/03/23/tsipras-visits-germany-for-first-time-as-greek-leader-as-countries-seek-to-mend/?utm_source=feedburner&amp;amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+foxbusiness%2Flatest+%28Internal+-+Latest+News+-+Text%29" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-23T07:30:08Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-23T07:30:08Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;BERLIN - Alexis Tsipras is visiting Germany for the first time since becoming Greece's prime minister as his debt-ridden country and its key creditor seek to halt a downward spiral in relations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last week, Merkel and other European leaders told Tsipras to come up soon with budget cuts and tax increases that would enable him to get more bailout money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tsipras' first few weeks in office have been marked by tensions over the two governments' contrasting approaches to the debt crisis and Athens' revival of calls for World War II reparations from Berlin.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-23T07:30:08Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Greek PM Tsipras says more optimistic after talks</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://finance.yahoo.com/news/greek-pm-tsipras-says-more-020334685.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-20T03:21:10Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-20T03:21:10Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;"I'm more optimistic after this deliberation. I think that all the sides confirmed their intention to try to do their best to overcome the difficulties of the Greek economy as soon as possible," Tsipras said on leaving the talks in Brussels.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-20T03:21:10Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://l.yimg.com/a/p/us/news/editorial/d/0c/d0c3eb8ca18907492a4b337b5cec5193.jpeg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Greek leader defiant ahead of bailout meeting</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://finance.yahoo.com/news/greek-leader-defiant-ahead-bailout-121756506.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-18T12:50:52Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-18T12:50:52Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Tsipras spoke in parliament before lawmakers approved an anti-poverty bill, the first piece of legislation from the left-wing government elected on Jan. 25.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-18T12:50:52Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://l1.yimg.com/bt/api/res/1.2/_LN_nUpZxGntu4W7r7SDSg--/YXBwaWQ9eW5ld3M7Zmk9ZmlsbDtoPTM3NztpbD1wbGFuZTtweG9mZj01MDtweW9mZj0wO3E9NzU7dz02NzA-/http://globalfinance.zenfs.com/images/US_AHTTP_AP_FINANCIALTIMES/b14c604767441d0c710f6a7067000c47_original.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Greek leader defiant ahead of bailout meeting</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://news.yahoo.com/greek-leader-defiant-ahead-bailout-meeting-121742716--finance.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-03-18T12:50:51Z</updated>
    <published>2015-03-18T12:50:51Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Although there has been no formal response to Tsipras' request for the emergency meeting with Merkel and Hollande, Greek government spokesman Gavriil Sakellaridis indicated that it would go ahead.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-03-18T12:50:51Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://l.yimg.com/bt/api/res/1.2/5b8ANgItztcOn4NllqqjPA--/YXBwaWQ9eW5ld3M7Zmk9ZmlsbDtoPTM3NztpbD1wbGFuZTtweG9mZj01MDtweW9mZj0wO3E9NzU7dz02NzA-/http://media.zenfs.com/en_us/News/ap_webfeeds/b14c604767441d0c710f6a7067000c47.jpg" />
  </entry>
</feed>
