<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
  <title>NewsTracker: state islamic</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://newstracker.github.io/timeline.state_islamic.xml" />
  <subtitle>This is a news tracking demo</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <title>During Ramadan, call for Islamic awakening resonates with Muslim scholars pushing for reform</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.startribune.com/muslim-scholars-use-ramadan-to-push-for-an-islamic-renewal/315688681/" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-16T06:55:15Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-16T06:55:15Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;But one of the Arab world's most famous Muslim televangelists, Amr Khaled, who dedicated his TV show through Ramadan to discussing ways of reform, pointed out that it has been at least 70 years since the last great work on Islamic jurisprudence was written.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-16T06:55:15Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Muslim scholars use Ramadan to push for an Islamic renewal</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/nation-world/world/article27378178.html%23storylink=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-16T06:54:44Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-16T06:54:44Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;On one level, the religious reform effort - known in Arabic as "tajdeed," or "renewal"- is aimed at drawing the faithful away from extremism at a time when militant violence has escalated in the region with the spread of the Islamic State group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The UAE's counterterrorism lectures, organized by Abu Dhabi's Islamic Affairs authority during the month of Ramadan, which ends Friday, drew more than 300 speakers, many of them from Cairo's al-Azhar.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-16T06:54:44Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.charlotteobserver.com/static/img/placeholder/FREE.gif" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>U.S. delivers Iraqi antiquities seized in raid on Islamic State</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://cnews.canoe.com/CNEWS/World/2015/07/15/22507376.html?cid=rssnewsworld" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-15T16:33:27Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-15T16:33:27Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;BAGHDAD - The United States handed back to Iraq on Wednesday antiquities it said it had seized in a raid on Islamic State fighters in Syria, saying the haul was proof the militants were funding their war by smuggling ancient treasures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The haul also included early Islamic coins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamic State, a hardline Sunni Islamist group, has ransacked some of the greatest archaeological sites in northern Iraq, posting video footage of fighters destroying pre-Islamic monuments they consider idolatrous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iraqi officials have been unable to verify the full extent of damage at the sites under Islamic State control, but they have said that footage of the destruction was published in part to distract attention from the fact Islamic State is smuggling antiquities to raise cash.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-15T16:33:27Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Egypt army says it foils attack on road to Red Sea coast</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/business/national-business/article27308440.html%23storylink=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-15T15:27:01Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-15T15:27:01Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Egypt's armed forces said they foiled an attempted attack Wednesday on a military post on a highway linking Cairo with the Red Sea coast that was claimed by Islamic State affiliates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Egypt faces threats from multiple insurgent factions, including the Islamic State affiliate in Sinai that the military says killed at least 17 soldiers in a July 1 assault there.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-15T15:27:01Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Rich nations worry about Islamic State; poor fear climate change: Pew survey</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.brisbanetimes.com.au/world/rich-nations-worry-about-islamic-state-poor-fear-climate-change-pew-survey-20150715-giczel.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-15T08:04:41Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-15T08:04:41Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The barbaric acts and military gains of Islamic State have succeeded in sowing fear in Australia and other wealthy nations, with a new poll showing the extremist group is considered the biggest global threat in all but one advanced economy surveyed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The poll, released overnight, found that Australia and nine other countries with advanced economies all ranked Islamic State (IS) as the biggest threat.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-15T08:04:41Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="ww.brisbanetimes.com.au/content/dam/images/g/i/9/4/f/e/image.related.articleLeadwide.620x349.giczel.png/1436947392590.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Boston police captain's son held without bail in Islamic State-inspired bomb plot</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://cnews.canoe.com/CNEWS/Crime/2015/07/14/22506011.html?cid=rssnewscrime" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-14T23:16:47Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-14T23:16:47Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The case follows a handful of "lone wolf" attacks in the United States and Canada since last year by people authorities say were inspired by Islamic State, which controls parts of Syria and Iraq and has vowed attacks on the West.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the post-arrest video played in court on Tuesday, Ciccolo did not detail an attack plot but defended Islamic State's hostage executions and agreed with an FBI interviewer that all Americans should be considered "enemies".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His attorney, David Hoose, said Ciccolo had so far only been charged with gun violations and that his views on Islamic State should not be considered.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-14T23:16:47Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://storage.canoe.com/v1/dynamic_resize/?src=http://cnews.canoe.com/CNEWS/Crime/2015/07/14/TCP_Ciccolo650.jpg&amp;amp;amp;size=650x366&amp;amp;amp;quality=85" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Son of Boston police captain charged in terror bomb plot</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/2015/jul/13/son-of-boston-police-captain-charged-in-terror/" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-13T18:28:42Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-13T18:28:42Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;BOSTON (AP) - Prosecutors have arrested the son of a Boston police captain in a plot to commit terrorist acts on behalf of the Islamic State group.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-13T18:28:42Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State claims Afghan leader alive after US airstrike</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.nzherald.co.nz/world/news/article.cfm?c_id=2&amp;amp;objectid=11480342&amp;amp;ref=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-13T11:35:17Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-13T11:35:17Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;In the audio, which was posted on known militant websites, a man speaking Pashtun calls on listeners to join the Islamic State group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Islamic State group's al-Bayan radio identified the man Monday as Sayeed, without elaborating.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-13T11:35:17Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State group releases audio claiming Afghan leader still alive after US airstrike</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.startribune.com/islamic-state-claims-afghan-leader-alive-after-us-airstrike/314521941/" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-13T11:30:09Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-13T11:30:09Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan - The Islamic State group released an online audio clip Monday they claim came from the leader of an Afghan affiliate that authorities there say was killed in a U.S. airstrike.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-13T11:30:09Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State attacks Syrian army and Kurds in twin assault</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/06/25/us-mideast-crisis-syria-idUSKBN0P50LA20150625?feedType=RSS&amp;amp;feedName=worldNews" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-25T21:17:05Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-25T21:17:05Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Syrian state TV said Islamic State was expelling residents from their homes in al-Nashwa, executing people and detaining them.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-25T21:17:05Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://s4.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?d=20150625&amp;amp;i=109106528&amp;amp;w=240&amp;amp;r=109106528-1&amp;amp;t=2" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State says behind bombing at Italian consulate in Cairo [Video]</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.torontosun.com/2015/07/11/islamic-state-says-behind-bombing-at-italian-consulate-in-cairo" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-11T21:31:44Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-11T21:31:44Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Until now, Islamic State supporters in Egypt had not set their sights on Western targets, focusing instead on security forces.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-11T21:31:44Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://storage.torontosun.com/v1/dynamic_resize/sws_path/suns-prod-images/1297723313087_ORIGINAL.jpg?quality=80&amp;amp;size=65x" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State scores up gains and losses in Syrian fighting</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/06/30/us-mideast-crisis-syria-idUSKCN0PA21F20150630?feedType=RSS&amp;amp;feedName=worldNews" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-30T20:07:37Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-30T20:07:37Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;"Islamic State had withdrawn from most of the districts but did not leave it completely and their snipers in some areas are preventing the full advance of the army," said Ali Hreith, a Hasaka resident on the Turkish-Syrian border.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-30T20:07:37Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://s2.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&amp;amp;d=20150630&amp;amp;t=2&amp;amp;i=1060412297&amp;amp;w=644&amp;amp;fh=&amp;amp;fw=&amp;amp;ll=&amp;amp;pl=&amp;amp;r=LYNXNPEB5T0WH" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Afghanistan says US strikes destroy its Islamic State branch</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.daytondailynews.com/ap/ap/international/activists-28-killed-in-syrian-army-strikes-on-is-h/nmxJJ/" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-11T17:39:03Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-11T17:39:03Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Afghanistan said Saturday that recent U.S. airstrikes it assisted destroyed the top leadership of a fledging Islamic State affiliate there, potentially striking a major blow to an insurgent group already targeted by local Taliban fighters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sediqi offered no photographs or other evidence to show the strikes killed the Islamic State affiliate's top leaders, though he said Afghan authorities verified a corpse from Friday's strike was Sayeed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disenchanted extremists from the Taliban and other organizations, impressed by the Islamic State group's territorial gains and slick online propaganda, began raising its black flag in extremist-dominated areas of both countries in recent months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Afghan officials have suggested the Islamic State affiliate had a presence in three of its provinces, including Nangarhar, which borders Pakistan and frequently sees militants cross its borders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sediqi, the National Directorate of Security spokesman, said Afghan officials had created a special intelligence unit to target the Islamic State affiliate and its work directly aided the U.S. airstrikes.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-11T17:39:03Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://media.cmgdigital.com/shared/lt/lt_cache/thumbnail/188/img/photos/2015/07/11/b0/8e/9e5d713208f445ab914d1643943c53ef-62e05bbd42c14c27918572962e340572-0.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>The Latest: Islamic State claims Italian Consulate blast</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.sfgate.com/news/world/article/The-Latest-Blast-at-Italian-Consulate-in-Cairo-6378938.php" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-11T15:46:57Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-11T15:46:57Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The claim, signed Islamic State Egypt, says the car contained 450 kilograms (990 pounds) of explosives.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-11T15:46:57Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://ww4.hdnux.com/photos/37/50/42/8292495/41/square_gallery_thumb.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State supporters circulate claim of responsibility for Cairo Italian Consulate bombing</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/2015/jul/11/islamic-state-supporters-circulate-claim-of/" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-11T15:33:07Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-11T15:33:07Z</published>
    <summary type="html" />
    <dc:date>2015-07-11T15:33:07Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Afghan official says that highest-ranking IS figure in Afghanistan killed in US strike</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.startribune.com/official-senior-islamic-state-figure-killed-in-a-us-strike/313684091/" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-11T11:25:07Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-11T11:25:07Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Taliban, at war with the government for nearly 14 years, have warned the Islamic State group to stay out.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-11T11:25:07Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Official: Senior Islamic State figure killed in a US strike</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.daytondailynews.com/ap/ap/international/official-senior-islamic-state-figure-killed-in-a-u/nmxJZ/" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-11T11:23:14Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-11T11:23:14Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The strike in Nangarhar province killed Islamic State affiliate leader Hafeez Sayeed and others on Friday, said Abdul Hassib Sediqi, a spokesman for Afghanistan's National Directorate of Security.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-11T11:23:14Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State kills at least 145 civilians in Syria's Kobani</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/06/26/us-mideast-crisis-syria-idUSKBN0P60UY20150626?feedType=RSS&amp;amp;feedName=wtMostRead" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-26T16:46:41Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-26T16:46:41Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;BEIRUT Islamic State fighters killed at least 145 civilians in an attack on the Syrian town of Kobani and a nearby village, in what a monitoring group described on Friday as one of the worst massacres carried out by the hardline group in Syria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike the Kobani raid, the Islamic State attack on Hasaka appears aimed at wresting control of the government-held parts of city, which is divided into areas run separately by President Bashar al-Assad's government and the YPG.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamic State pressed a separate assault to capture government-held parts of the northeastern city of Hasaka, blowing up a security building and triggering a government appeal for all residents to take up arms.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-26T16:46:41Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>IS beheads two women in Syria: monitor</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://news.yahoo.com/first-beheads-two-women-syria-monitor-073538672.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-30T08:20:54Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-30T08:20:54Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;"The Islamic State group executed two women by beheading them in Deir Ezzor province, and this is the first time the Observatory has documented women being killed by the group in this manner," Observatory chief Rami Abdel Rahman said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Islamic State group has become infamous for gruesome executions and is reported to have stoned women to death on allegations of adultery.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-30T08:20:54Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>FBI says it thwarted Islamic State-inspired July 4 attacks</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/07/09/us-usa-security-fourth-idUSKCN0PJ2AU20150709?feedType=RSS&amp;amp;feedName=topNews" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-09T21:26:23Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-09T21:26:23Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Separately, a national security source said multiple overseas plots by Islamic State sympathizers had also been halted in recent days.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-09T21:26:23Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>FBI says it thwarted Islamic State-inspired July 4 attacks</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/07/09/us-usa-security-fourth-idUSKCN0PJ2AU20150709?feedType=RSS&amp;amp;feedName=wtMostRead" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-09T21:26:23Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-09T21:26:23Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Some of those arrested were communicating with Islamic State via encrypted data, a second U.S. security source said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comey estimated that dozens of people influenced by Islamic State have "gone dark" and disappeared from the FBI's watch because of encrypted data.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-09T21:26:23Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Afghan spy agency says third Islamic State commander killed in drone strike</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/07/09/us-afghanistan-attack-idUSKCN0PJ1IR20150709?feedType=RSS&amp;amp;feedName=worldNews" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-09T13:05:42Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-09T13:05:42Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;KABUL The Afghan intelligence agency on Thursday said a third top Islamic State commander in Afghanistan was killed in a U.S. drone strike in the country's east this week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shahid was killed in the same strike that killed Islamic State number two in Afghanistan Gul Zaman, along with 49 militants in the eastern Achin district of Nangarhar province where Islamic State militants have recently gained ground after pushing out the Taliban.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A small but increasing number of mostly ex-Taliban militants are pledging allegiance to the Islamic State in Afghanistan, making them a target of deadly strikes there by the U.S. unmanned aircraft.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-09T13:05:42Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>FBI chief warns encryption emboldens would-be Islamic State attackers</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/07/08/us-usa-fbi-islamic-state-idUSKCN0PI24J20150708?feedType=RSS&amp;amp;feedName=technologyNews" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-08T20:13:44Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-08T20:13:44Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Comey told a U.S. Senate Judiciary Committee hearing that Islamic State, also known by the acronym ISIL, is imploring supporters through Twitter to carry out attacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comey later told the Senate Select Committee on Intelligence that the FBI now estimated more than 200 Americans have traveled or attempted to travel to Syria to fight for Islamic militants.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-08T20:13:44Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>A secret to IS success: Shock troops who fight to the death</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/nation-world/world/article26719306.html%23storylink=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-08T06:54:51Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-08T06:54:51Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;"People go to the Islamic State looking to die, and the Islamic State is happy to help them."&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-08T06:54:51Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.charlotteobserver.com/static/img/placeholder/FREE.gif" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>A Secret to IS Success: Shock Troops Who Fight to the Death</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/secret-success-shock-troops-fight-death-32291952" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-08T06:52:04Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-08T06:52:04Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;They are the Islamic State group's elite shock troops.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though best known for its horrific brutalities, the Islamic State group has proved to be a highly organized and flexible fighting force, according to senior Iraqi military and intelligence officials and Syrian Kurdish commanders on the front lines.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-08T06:52:04Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>A secret to IS success: Shock troops who fight to the death</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2015/07/08/a-secret-to-is-success-shock-troops-who-fight-to-the-death" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-08T06:50:25Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-08T06:50:25Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;BAGHDAD (AP) - Bearded and wearing bright blue bandanas, the Islamic State group's "special forces" unit gathered around their commander just before they attacked the central Syrian town of al-Sukhna.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-08T06:50:25Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>US military chiefs face tough questioning from senators</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.sfgate.com/news/article/US-military-chiefs-face-tough-questioning-from-6370308.php" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-07T16:33:58Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-07T16:33:58Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Carter backed the president's policy while acknowledging that more needs to be done to strengthen the mission to train local forces to combat the Islamic extremists.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-07T16:33:58Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://ww1.hdnux.com/photos/37/43/11/8270400/5/square_gallery_thumb.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Spanish woman arrested for recruiting girls, teens for IS</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/nation-world/world/article26647843.html%23storylink=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-07T16:25:04Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-07T16:25:04Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The ministry said the woman in Arrecife maintained contact with Islamic State militants in Syria, including a facilitator who gave her orders for recruiting girls and arranging their travel to Syria.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-07T16:25:04Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>US military chiefs face tough questioning on Islamic State</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://news.yahoo.com/us-military-chiefs-face-tough-questioning-islamic-state-140322065.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-07T16:24:05Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-07T16:24:05Z</published>
    <summary type="html" />
    <dc:date>2015-07-07T16:24:05Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://l.yimg.com/os/mit/media/m/base/images/transparent-649ba6f.png" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>US military chiefs face tough questioning on Islamic State</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.nzherald.co.nz/world/news/article.cfm?c_id=2&amp;amp;objectid=11477255&amp;amp;ref=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-07T16:10:16Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-07T16:10:16Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;McCain said Islamic State continues to gain territory in Iraq and Syria, while expanding its influence across the Middle East, Africa and Central Asia.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-07T16:10:16Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Spanish woman arrested for recruiting girls to Islamic State</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.ctvnews.ca/world/spanish-woman-arrested-for-recruiting-girls-to-islamic-state-1.2457443" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-07T14:29:40Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-07T14:29:40Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;MADRID -- Spanish police on Tuesday arrested a woman suspected of recruiting pre-teen girls and teenagers to send to areas controlled by the Islamic State armed group in Syria.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-07T14:29:40Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Syrian Kurds retake northern villages from Islamic State: monitor</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/07/07/us-mideast-crisis-syria-idUSKCN0PH0SJ20150707?feedType=RSS&amp;amp;feedName=topNews" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-07T13:19:15Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-07T13:19:15Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The YPG, backed by small Syrian rebel groups, has made significant gains against Islamic State in Raqqa province in recent weeks, seizing Tel Abyad at the Turkish border on June 15 before advancing south to Ain Issa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the YPG has shown itself to be a potent force in the fight against Islamic State, its effectiveness is seen to diminish beyond the predominantly Kurdish areas it was set up to defend in northern and northeastern Syria.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-07T13:19:15Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Kenya says Islamic extremists kill 14 in Kenya's north</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/2015/jul/06/kenya-says-islamic-extremists-kill-14-in-kenyas/" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-07T05:46:24Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-07T05:46:24Z</published>
    <summary type="html" />
    <dc:date>2015-07-07T05:46:24Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>HSBC bank staff sacked for Islamic State beheading prank</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.smh.com.au/world/hsbc-bank-staff-sacked-for-islamic-state-beheading-prank-20150707-gi6mjw.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-07T05:15:44Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-07T05:15:44Z</published>
    <summary type="html" />
    <dc:date>2015-07-07T05:15:44Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="ww.smh.com.au/content/dam/images/g/g/y/o/c/e/image.related.thumbnail.90x60.gi6mjw.png/1436246120385.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>HSBC fires 6 staff for mock Islamic State execution video</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/world/uk/HSBC-fires-6-staff-for-mock-Islamic-State-execution-video/articleshow/47968514.cms" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-07T04:37:02Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-07T04:37:02Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;British bank HSBC fired six staff after they filmed a mock Islamic State-style execution video during a team-building day out and posted footage online, a spokesman confirmed on Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-07T04:37:02Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/thumb/msid-47968619,width-300,resizemode-4/HSBC.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Obama at Pentagon for meetings on Islamic State</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.miamiherald.com/news/politics-government/article26569714.html%23storylink=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-06T19:34:07Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-06T19:34:07Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;President Barack Obama, right, sits next to Defense Secretary Ash Carter, with other military personnel as they wait to receives an update on the Islamic State group at the Pentagon on Monday, July 6, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-06T19:34:07Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.miamiherald.com/static/img/placeholder/FREE.gif" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Israel arrests 6 Bedouin for supporting Islamic State group</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.nzherald.co.nz/world/news/article.cfm?c_id=2&amp;amp;objectid=11476800&amp;amp;ref=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-06T18:15:18Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-06T18:15:18Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;JERUSALEM (AP) " Israel's Shin Bet security agency says it has arrested six Bedouin for establishing a cell supportive of the Islamic State group.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-06T18:15:18Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Israel Arrests 6 Bedouin for Supporting Islamic State Group</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/israel-arrests-bedouin-supporting-islamic-state-group-32255857" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-06T18:11:15Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-06T18:11:15Z</published>
    <summary type="html" />
    <dc:date>2015-07-06T18:11:15Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>White House criticizes Senate for not approving appointments to counter Islamic State</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/07/06/us-usa-congress-whitehouse-idUSKCN0PG1YK20150706?feedType=RSS&amp;amp;feedName=politicsNews" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-06T17:40:57Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-06T17:40:57Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON The White House criticized Republicans in the U.S. Senate on Monday for not approving appointments aimed at fighting the Islamic State.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-06T17:40:57Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Obama heads to Pentagon for meetings on Islamic State</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.daytondailynews.com/ap/ap/top-news/obama-heads-to-pentagon-for-meetings-on-islamic-st/nmsCy/" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-06T17:34:22Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-06T17:34:22Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;President Barack Obama will pay a rare visit to the Pentagon on Monday to get an update from military leaders on the campaign against the Islamic State.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-06T17:34:22Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://media.cmgdigital.com/shared/lt/lt_cache/thumbnail/188/img/photos/2015/07/06/c1/7c/f12e0f8660fd457fabfce7e64db68146-1f89a77dcb6d4272ab245f40a9173b36-0_1.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Kuwait detains 26 over Islamic State suicide attack on mosque -newspaper</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/world/middle-east/Kuwait-detains-26-over-Islamic-State-suicide-attack-on-mosque-newspaper/articleshow/47962135.cms" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-06T14:46:33Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-06T14:46:33Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The June 26 attack by Islamic State militants jolted Kuwait, raising the spectre of sectarian strife in the Gulf Arab oil exporting state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He said other suspects, including fighters with Islamic State abroad, have been identified and that some of their relatives inside Kuwait have been charged in connection with the blast.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-06T14:46:33Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/thumb/msid-47962230,width-300,resizemode-4/kuwait.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State suicide bombers strike in Iraqi refinery town</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/07/05/us-mideast-crisis-iraq-idUSKCN0PF0EA20150705?feedType=RSS&amp;amp;feedName=worldNews" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-05T15:29:22Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-05T15:29:22Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The latest Islamic State offensive comes after authorities said they controlled nearly the whole town and expected to drive insurgents from the refinery within days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baiji mayor Mahmoud al-Jabouri said there had been a pattern of withdrawals by Islamic State fighters in the town followed by counter-offensives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Islamic State fighters are still holding positions in three neighborhoods in Baiji and they are still receiving reinforcements," said one of the army colonels.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-05T15:29:22Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State attacks Syrian army and Kurds in twin assault</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://news.yahoo.com/islamic-state-attacks-syrian-army-kurds-offensive-064241784.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-25T18:27:03Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-25T18:27:03Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Islamic State advanced rapidly last month, seizing cities in Syria and Iraq.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-25T18:27:03Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://l.yimg.com/bt/api/res/1.2/cYI.VUZ6hVEPM9tvGDZYhQ--/YXBwaWQ9eW5ld3M7Zmk9ZmlsbDtoPTE5MztxPTc1O3c9MzAw/http://media.zenfs.com/en_us/News/Reuters/2015-06-25T150628Z_1_LYNXMPEB5O0RZ_RTROPTP_2_MIDEAST-CRISIS-SYRIA.JPG" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Deadly strikes by US-led coalition targeting IS in Raqqa</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.sandiegouniontribune.com/news/2015/jul/05/deadly-strikes-by-us-led-coalition-targeting-is/" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-05T09:45:10Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-05T09:45:10Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The airstrikes were confirmed by the coalition, Raqqa-base activists and the Islamic State group.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-05T09:45:10Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State says it destroyed archaeological pieces from Palmyra</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2015/07/03/islamic-state-palmyra/29661517/?utm_source=feedblitz&amp;amp;utm_medium=FeedBlitzRss&amp;amp;utm_campaign=usatodaycomworld-topstories" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-03T14:26:35Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-03T14:26:35Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Islamic State group says it has destroyed six archaeological pieces from the historic town of Palmyra that were confiscated from a smuggler.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An IS statement says the busts were found when the smuggler was stopped at a checkpoint and was later referred to an Islamic which ordered that they be destroyed and the man be whipped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The issue was referred to an Islamic court in the northern Syrian town of Manbij, which ordered that they be destroyed and the man be whipped.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-03T14:26:35Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.gannett-cdn.com/-mm-/92635442f11dad24e23e53632f3882005744472e/c=307-0-2000-1273&amp;amp;amp;r=x404&amp;amp;amp;c=534x401/local/-/media/USATODAY/WiresImages/2015/07/03/ccb475519f09231d7b0f6a7067000a7b.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>U.S. Drone Strike Kills Senior ISIS Leader</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://time.com/3945381/us-drone-isis-islamic-state-leader-dead/?utm_source=feedburner&amp;amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+time%2Fworld+%28TIME%3A+Top+World+Stories%29" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-03T02:27:04Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-03T02:27:04Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;(WASHINGTON) - A coalition airstrike in Syria has killed a senior Islamic State leader, who has been responsible for moving fighters and weapons from Libya to Syria, the Pentagon said Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Davis said al-Harzi's death will hurt the Islamic State's ability to move foreign fighters in and out of the region.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last September, the U.S. Treasury Department imposed economic sanctions on al-Harzi and seven other individuals that it said have helped finance or facilitate the movement of foreign fighters joining the Islamic State and the Nusra Front.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-03T02:27:04Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="https://timedotcom.files.wordpress.com/2015/07/mideast-syria-islamic_wong.jpg?quality=65&amp;amp;amp;strip=color&amp;amp;amp;w=550" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>U.S. drone strike kills senior Islamic State leader</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.torontosun.com/2015/07/02/us-drone-strike-kills-senior-islamic-state-leader" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-03T02:01:21Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-03T02:01:21Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Treasury statement identified him as the Islamic State group's "amir of suicide bombers," saying he recruited foreign fighters for suicide attacks in Iraq and Syria.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-03T02:01:21Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Syrian Kurds, on the offensive, push deeper into Islamic State territory</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/06/22/us-mideast-crisis-syria-kurds-idUSKBN0P21HV20150622?feedType=RSS&amp;amp;feedName=worldNews" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-22T15:14:11Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-22T15:14:11Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;A spokesman for the Pentagon said last week Islamic State forces had appeared to "crack" at the Turkish border town of Tel Abyad, which fell to the YPG in less than two days, cutting Islamic State's supply route from Turkey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Kurdish front in northern Syria has been one of the few sources of good news for the global campaign against Islamic State since the jihadists made major advances last month in western Iraq and central Syria.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-22T15:14:11Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://s4.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&amp;amp;d=20150622&amp;amp;t=2&amp;amp;i=1058220867&amp;amp;w=644&amp;amp;fh=&amp;amp;fw=&amp;amp;ll=&amp;amp;pl=&amp;amp;r=LYNXMPEB5L0M8" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State threatens to topple Hamas in Gaza</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/06/30/us-palestinians-islamicstate-hamas-idUSKCN0PA2TR20150630?feedType=RSS&amp;amp;feedName=worldNews" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-30T20:39:27Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-30T20:39:27Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;"At the same time, within Gaza, ISIS (Islamic State) has been flouting Hamas. But they have common cause against the Jews, in Israel or abroad."&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-30T20:39:27Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State beheads female civilians for first time in Syria for 'sorcery': monitor</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.brisbanetimes.com.au/world/islamic-state-beheads-female-civilians-for-first-time-in-syria-for-sorcery-monitor-20150630-gi1ztw" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-30T19:05:07Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-30T19:05:07Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;A member to the Islamic State in Iraq and the Levant (ISIL) waves an ISIL flag in Raqqa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamic State also "crucified" five men in al-Mayadeen for eating during daylight hours of the Muslim fasting month of Ramadan, the Observatory said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activists say Islamic State uses such public punishments in areas where it is present to control the local population through coercion and fear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australian Reece Harding killed fighting Islamic...&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-30T19:05:07Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="ww.brisbanetimes.com.au/content/dam/images/g/h/4/x/6/0/image.related.articleLeadwide.620x349.gi1ztw.png/1435697487854.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Syrian troops regain neighborhood they lost earlier in battles with Islamic State group</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.startribune.com/syrian-troops-regain-area-from-is-in-northeastern-city/310927191/" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-30T13:45:46Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-30T13:45:46Z</published>
    <summary type="html" />
    <dc:date>2015-06-30T13:45:46Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>France links beheading, gas plant attack to Islamic State</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.daytondailynews.com/ap/ap/international/prosecutor-beheading-french-factory-attack-is-trad/nmpB8/" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-30T12:30:43Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-30T12:30:43Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;French investigators have uncovered links between Islamic State militants and the man who hung his employer's severed head at a gas plant he was attacking, a prosecutor said Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then Salhi, a truck driver with a history of radical Islamic ties dating back to 2003, drove into the plant filled with flammable gas canisters, Molins said.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-30T12:30:43Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Prosecutor: Beheading, French gas plant attack Islamic State trademark</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://da.feedsportal.com/c/34253/f/622809/s/47b35322/sc/3/l/0L0Schicagotribune0N0Cct0Efrench0Ebeheading0Eattack0E20A150A630A0Estory0Bhtml/ia1.htm" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-30T10:50:00Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-30T10:50:00Z</published>
    <summary type="html" />
    <dc:date>2015-06-30T10:50:00Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State beheads women civilians for first time in Syria</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.abc.net.au/news/2015-06-30/islamic-state-beheads-women-civilians-for-first-time-in-syria/6585042" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-30T08:34:27Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-30T08:34:27Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Islamic State has beheaded local and foreign men in Syria, including enemy combatants, aid workers and journalists as well as people it has deemed as violating its hardline interpretation of Islamic law.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-30T08:34:27Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State seen as potent force a year after caliphate declaration: Pentagon</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://news.yahoo.com/islamic-state-seen-potent-force-caliphate-declaration-pentagon-193306168.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-29T19:33:06Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-29T19:33:06Z</published>
    <summary type="html" />
    <dc:date>2015-06-29T19:33:06Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://l2.yimg.com/bt/api/res/1.2/xpelNWLw6bEDa1romqQMag--/YXBwaWQ9eW5ld3M7Zmk9ZmlsbDtoPTE4MjtxPTc1O3c9MzAw/http://media.zenfs.com/en_us/News/Reuters/2015-06-29T193306Z_1007000001_LYNXNPEB5S14K_RTROPTP_2_CNEWS-US-MIDEAST-CRISIS-PENTAGON.JPG" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Mali: Gunmen attack village near Ivory Coast border</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2015/06/28/mali-gunmen-attack-village-near-ivory-coast-border" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-28T17:31:47Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-28T17:31:47Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Islamic extremists took control of northern Mali in 2012 following a military coup.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-28T17:31:47Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Mali: Gunmen attack village near Ivory Coast border</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.nzherald.co.nz/world/news/article.cfm?c_id=2&amp;amp;objectid=11472695&amp;amp;ref=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-28T17:25:16Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-28T17:25:16Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;BAMAKO, Mali (AP) " Gunmen identifying as Islamic extremists attacked and briefly occupied a village in southern Mali near Ivory Coast on Sunday before security forces drove them out, officials said.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-28T17:25:16Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Afghan official: Islamic State group now present in 3 provinces</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.startribune.com/afghan-official-is-group-present-in-at-least-3-provinces/310449971/" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-28T12:10:10Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-28T12:10:10Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;KABUL, Afghanistan - An Afghan official says the Islamic State group now has a presence in three provinces but that the government is determined to drive it out.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-28T12:10:10Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Report: Islamic State Claims Credit for Attack at Tunisian Resort That Killed at Least 37</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/report-islamic-state-claims-credit-attack-tunisian-resort-32063835" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-26T23:57:28Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-26T23:57:28Z</published>
    <summary type="html" />
    <dc:date>2015-06-26T23:57:28Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://a.abcnews.com/images/International/ap_tunisia_5_kb_150626_4x3t_96.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State suicide bomber kills 25, wounds 202 in Kuwait mosque</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.torontosun.com/2015/06/26/islamic-state-suicide-bomber-kills-more-than-10-in-kuwait-mosque" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-26T23:16:23Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-26T23:16:23Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Islamic State had urged its followers on Tuesday to step up attacks during the Ramadan fasting month against Christians, Shi'ites and Sunni Muslims fighting with a U.S.-led coalition against the ultra-hardline jihadist group.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-26T23:16:23Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://storage.torontosun.com/v1/dynamic_resize/sws_path/suns-prod-images/1297717188405_ORIGINAL.jpg?quality=80&amp;amp;size=420x" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State suicide bomber kills 27, wounds 227 in Kuwait mosque</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/06/26/us-kuwait-blast-idUSKBN0P618L20150626?feedType=RSS&amp;amp;feedName=topNews" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-26T22:44:54Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-26T22:44:54Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Islamic State militant group claimed responsibility for the attack, which also wounded 227 people according to the interior ministry, in the district of Sawaber in the eastern part of the Kuwaiti capital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamic State named the bomber as Abu Suleiman al-Muwahed and said in a statement posted on social media that he had targeted a "temple of the rejectionists" -- a term it generally uses to refer to Shi'ites, whom it regards as heretics.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-26T22:44:54Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State hits Shiite mosque in Kuwait, killing 27 people</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.sfgate.com/world/article/Islamic-State-hits-Shiite-mosque-in-Kuwait-6352210.php" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-26T21:33:03Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-26T21:33:03Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;A posting on a Twitter account known to belong to the Islamic State affiliate that calls itself the Najd Province, claimed the explosion was the work of a suicide bomber.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-26T21:33:03Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://ww2.hdnux.com/photos/37/26/70/8220193/3/square_gallery_thumb.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>French beheading suspect previously investigated for radical Islamic ties</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://tvnz.co.nz/world-news/french-beheading-suspect-previously-investigated-radical-islamic-ties-6347844?ref=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-26T20:47:00Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-26T20:47:00Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;followed a call by Islamic State extremists to target "nonbelievers."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The severed head appeared to mimic the Islamic State group's practice of beheading prisoners and displaying their heads for all to see, and came days after the militants urged attacks during the Muslim holy month of Ramadan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A knife and the decapitated body of Salhi's employer were found at the site of the explosion, and the severed head was posted on a gate at the factory entrance with two flags bearing proclamations of Islamic faith, the prosecutor said.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-26T20:47:00Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State kills at least 145 civilians in Syria's Kobani</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/06/26/us-mideast-crisis-syria-idUSKBN0P60UY20150626?feedType=RSS&amp;amp;feedName=topNews" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-26T16:46:41Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-26T16:46:41Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;While Islamic State had managed to advance slightly in Hasaka on Friday, seizing one army position, fierce army air strikes had hindered the attack, Abdulrahman said.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-26T16:46:41Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>O'Malley: Islamic State a result of 'mindless rush to war'</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.daytondailynews.com/ap/ap/top-news/omalley-islamic-state-rise-unintended-result-from-/nmmW9/" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-26T16:32:04Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-26T16:32:04Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Democratic presidential candidate Martin O'Malley said Friday the rise of the Islamic State group was an unintended consequence of a "mindless rush to war" in Iraq and the U.S. must avoid "mission creep" there now.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-26T16:32:04Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State affiliate strikes Shiite mosque in Kuwait, killing 27 people</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.theglobeandmail.com/news/world/deadly-explosion-strikes-shiite-mosque-in-kuwaits-capital-after-friday-prayers/article25129105/?cmpid=rss1" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-26T11:48:16Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-26T11:48:16Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The attack, which hit the capital of Kuwait City, was one of three deadly attacks from Europe to the Middle East on Friday that followed the Islamic State group's call for violence during the Muslim holy month of Ramadan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Islamic State extremists regard Shiite Muslims as heretics, and refer to them derogatively as "rejectionists."&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-26T11:48:16Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Vladimir Putin calls Barack Obama to discuss Ukraine and Islamic State</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/worldnews/vladimir-putin/11700224/Vladimir-Putin-calls-Barack-Obama-to-discuss-Ukraine-and-Islamic-State.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-25T23:42:53Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-25T23:42:53Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Obama and Putin also discussed Syria, where the self-proclaimed Islamic State group has made rapid gains, as well as historic negotiations between world powers and Iran over its disputed nuclear programme.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-25T23:42:53Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://i.telegraph.co.uk/multimedia/archive/02637/obama-putin_2637988b.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State Militants Attack 2 Cities in Northern Syria</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/turk-officials-islamic-state-group-attack-kobani-32014335" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-25T19:34:29Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-25T19:34:29Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;After weeks of setbacks, militants from the Islamic State group launched swift counteroffensives Thursday on predominantly Kurdish areas of northern Syria, killing and wounding dozens and setting off car bombs, activists and officials said.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-25T19:34:29Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://a.abcnews.com/assets/images/navigation/abc-logo.png" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State militants attack 2 cities in northern Syria</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.sfgate.com/news/world/article/Turk-officials-Islamic-State-group-in-new-attack-6348165.php" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-25T19:33:13Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-25T19:33:13Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Turkish officials said on Thursday, June 25, 2015 that the Islamic State group has staged a new attack on the Kurdish town of Kobani, which resisted a months-long assault by the Islamic militants until they were pushed out earlier this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two-pronged attack on the northeastern city of Hassakeh and the border town of Kobani came two days after an Islamic State spokesman acknowledged that the group might lose some battles but would not be defeated.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-25T19:33:13Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://ww3.hdnux.com/photos/37/25/20/8213522/7/920x920.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>North Carolina man charged in plot to kill Americans for Islamic State</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://news.yahoo.com/north-carolina-man-charged-gun-plot-kill-americans-151022785.html" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-22T17:26:04Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-22T17:26:04Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (Reuters) - A North Carolina man has been charged with an alleged plot to buy a semiautomatic rifle which he planned to use to kill Americans to show his support for the Islamic State militant group, the U.S. Department of Justice said on Monday.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-22T17:26:04Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://l.yimg.com/bt/api/res/1.2/_Og6neefqiJYHg4pYMtPfg--/YXBwaWQ9eW5ld3M7Zmk9ZmlsbDtoPTM3NztpbD1wbGFuZTtweG9mZj01MDtweW9mZj0wO3E9NzU7dz02NzA-/http://media.zenfs.com/en_us/News/ap_webfeeds/d88014a6d57cca17770f6a706700b34e.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Officials: North Carolina Teen Planned to Help ISIS</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.usnews.com/news/articles/2015/06/22/fbi-arrests-north-carolina-teen-accused-of-helping-isis" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-22T16:48:39Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-22T16:48:39Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;CHARLOTTE, N.C. (AP) - A North Carolina man is in the custody of federal authorities, who say he planned assassinations in the United States in support of the Islamic State terrorist group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Federal authorities said in a news release Monday that 19-year-old Justin Nojan Sullivan of Morganton faces several charges, including one count of attempting to provide material support to the Islamic State group.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-22T16:48:39Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Europol to battle Islamic State social media propaganda</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.sfgate.com/news/world/article/Europol-to-battle-IS-propaganda-on-social-media-6341574.php" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-22T15:55:29Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-22T15:55:29Z</published>
    <summary type="html" />
    <dc:date>2015-06-22T15:55:29Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://ww2.hdnux.com/photos/37/20/50/8194605/7/920x920.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Syrian Kurds, on the offensive, push deeper into Islamic State territory</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.reuters.com/article/2015/06/22/us-mideast-crisis-syria-kurds-idUSKBN0P21HV20150622?feedType=RSS&amp;amp;feedName=topNews" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-22T15:14:11Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-22T15:14:11Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Islamic State has held the base, "Liwa 93", since capturing it from the Syrian military last year.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-22T15:14:11Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://s4.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&amp;amp;d=20150622&amp;amp;t=2&amp;amp;i=1058220867&amp;amp;w=644&amp;amp;fh=&amp;amp;fw=&amp;amp;ll=&amp;amp;pl=&amp;amp;r=LYNXMPEB5L0M8" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>A short chronology of the Islamic State group</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.miamiherald.com/news/nation-world/article25104442.html%23storylink=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-21T12:10:06Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-21T12:10:06Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;In areas controlled by the Islamic State group in Iraq and Syria, women must not only be covered, but usually are required to wear all black, with flat-soled shoes; for men, Western clothes or hair styles - even hair gel - can draw suspicion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FILE - This undated file image made from a video released by Islamic State militants Tuesday, Aug. 19, 2014, purports to show the killing of journalist James Foley by the militant group.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-21T12:10:06Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.miamiherald.com/static/img/placeholder/FREE.gif" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>A short chronology of the Islamic State group</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/nation-world/national/article25104442.html%23storylink=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-21T12:10:06Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-21T12:10:06Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;June 16, 2015 - Kurds deal the Islamic State a major setback by capturing the Syrian town of Tal Abyad on the Turkish border, which had provided a strategic supply route to IS.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-21T12:10:06Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.charlotteobserver.com/static/img/placeholder/FREE.gif" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Sunni Tribes, Abandoned by Iraq, Key to Islamic State Fight</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://abcnews.go.com/International/wireStory/sunni-tribes-abandoned-iraq-key-islamic-state-fight-31912317" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-20T21:22:38Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-20T21:22:38Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Parading across a desert base, hundreds of Sunni tribesmen who graduated a crash training course stood ready to take on the Islamic State group on behalf of a government that many believed left them to die at the hands of the extremists.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-20T21:22:38Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Sunni tribes, abandoned by Iraq, key to Islamic State fight</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/nation-world/world/article25085614.html%23storylink=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-20T16:54:00Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-20T16:54:00Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Islamic State group has massacred hundreds of men, women and children with Anbar's Al Bu Nimr tribe for resisting their rule and cooperating with the Iraqi government.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-20T16:54:00Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://www.charlotteobserver.com/static/img/placeholder/FREE.gif" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State-claimed car bombing kills 2 in Yemen's capital</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.sfgate.com/news/world/article/Yemeni-officials-say-car-bomb-exploded-in-Sanaa-6339154.php" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-20T18:33:14Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-20T18:33:14Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Islamic State group claimed the attack on a Twitter account associated with the extremists, saying it targeted Shiite Houthis, who the Sunni extremists view as heretics.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-20T18:33:14Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://ww1.hdnux.com/photos/37/16/51/8186436/7/square_gallery_thumb.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Islamic State-claimed car bombing kills 2 in Yemen's capital</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2015/06/20/yemeni-officials-say-car-bomb-exploded-in-sanaa" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-20T18:33:14Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-20T18:33:14Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;SANAA, Yemen (AP) - An Islamic State-claimed car bomb exploded outside a mosque in Yemen's capital Saturday, killing at least two people and wounding six amid the country's raging civil war, authorities said.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-20T18:33:14Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Sunni tribes, abandoned by Iraq, key to Islamic State fight</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2015/06/20/sunni-tribes-abandoned-by-iraq-key-to-islamic-state-fight" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-20T16:24:55Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-20T16:24:55Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;That night, silence fell over Ramadi after weeks of Islamic State-launched suicide car bomb attacks and gun battles, said Sunni tribesmen who spoke to The Associated Press.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet despite being targeting by the Islamic State group, many of the Sunni tribesmen from Anbar who spoke to the AP said the Baghdad government viewed them as being complicit in the extremists' advance, solely because they share the same sect.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-20T16:24:55Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Sunni tribes, abandoned by Iraq, key to Islamic State fight</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.utsandiego.com/news/2015/jun/20/sunni-tribes-abandoned-by-iraq-key-to-islamic/" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-06-20T16:24:55Z</updated>
    <published>2015-06-20T16:24:55Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;But money and weapons alone won't be enough to repair the mistrust between Baghdad and the Sunni tribes it now needs to battle the Islamic State group, which holds about a third of the country and neighboring Syria in its self-declared "caliphate."&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-06-20T16:24:55Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://media.utsandiego.com/img/photos/2015/06/20/e95b49458865ef1b790f6a7067006572_r620x349.JPEG?75d51d0aea2efce5189afce216053cbc530c46a8" />
  </entry>
</feed>
