<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
  <title>NewsTracker: ebola</title>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://newstracker.github.io/timeline.ebola.xml" />
  <subtitle>This is a news tracking demo</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <title>As Ebola cases decline, ZMapp drug trial answers unclear</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.cbc.ca/news/health/as-ebola-cases-decline-zmapp-drug-trial-answers-unclear-1.3191049?cmp=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-08-14T14:06:09Z</updated>
    <published>2015-08-14T14:06:09Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Moments after the first person treated with ZMapp started receiving the experimental Ebola drug he could feel effects which suggested it was working.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A study of another drug, TKM-Ebola, was stopped when its Data and Safety Monitoring Board concluded there was no hope giving it to more people would show it was effective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lane says he had anticipated that an answer would be found when the trial had enrolled somewhere between 40 and 100 Ebola patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They argue ZMapp cannot save Ebola patients who are too far along in the disease, so enrolling them in the study makes it harder to see if and how well the drug works.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-08-14T14:06:09Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://i.cbc.ca/1.2811548.1414156445!/fileImage/httpImage/image.jpg_gen/derivatives/original_300/who-ebola-marie-paule-kieny.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>UN official: Ebola epidemic could be defeated by end of 2015</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.sfgate.com/news/us/article/UN-official-Ebola-epidemic-could-be-defeated-by-6442438.php" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-08-13T16:50:04Z</updated>
    <published>2015-08-13T16:50:04Z</published>
    <summary type="html" />
    <dc:date>2015-08-13T16:50:04Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Ebola epidemic could be defeated by end of 2015: UN health chief</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.ctvnews.ca/health/ebola-epidemic-could-be-defeated-by-end-of-2015-un-health-chief-1.2515327" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-08-13T15:56:00Z</updated>
    <published>2015-08-13T15:56:00Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Ebola epidemic in West Africa can be defeated by the end of the year if the number of new cases drops to zero and stays at zero, the head of the World Health Organization said Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fears that the Ebola virus could be permanently established in humans in the region have also been defeated, which is also "very good news," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She predicted that there would be further setbacks like the flare-up of Ebola at the end of June in Liberia, nearly two months after the country was declared Ebola-free.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-08-13T15:56:00Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>China pledges continued support for Ebola-hit Africa nations</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.chron.com/news/medical/article/China-pledges-continued-support-for-Ebola-hit-6434945.php" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-08-10T12:59:35Z</updated>
    <published>2015-08-10T12:59:35Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;MONROVIA, Liberia (AP) - China's foreign minister has pledged continued support to the three West African countries hardest hit by the Ebola outbreak that has killed more than 11,200 people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China was one of the first to fly in badly needed medical gear when Ebola spread last year.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-08-10T12:59:35Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Sierra Leone Ebola head says country has 4 cases</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.daytondailynews.com/ap/ap/top-news/sierra-leone-ebola-head-says-country-has-4-cases/nnDyh/" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-08-06T15:53:14Z</updated>
    <published>2015-08-06T15:53:14Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Sierra Leone has only four recorded cases of Ebola, the West African nation's head of Ebola said Thursday, adding that he is hopeful the countdown to zero can soon begin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Authorities last week quarantined 500 people after a man died from Ebola.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-08-06T15:53:14Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>UN says new Ebola cases in single digits another week</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.ctvnews.ca/health/un-says-new-ebola-cases-in-single-digits-another-week-1.2503480" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-08-05T18:44:00Z</updated>
    <published>2015-08-05T18:44:00Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The path to zero cases, however, remains a challenge as the West African nations that have seen most of the more than 11,200 deaths from Ebola -- Sierra Leone, Guinea and Liberia -- head into rainy season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHO reported two confirmed cases of Ebola --one in Guinea and one in Sierra Leone-- in the week ending Aug. 2.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-08-05T18:44:00Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>New Ebola cases in single digits another week, says WHO</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.usnews.com/news/world/articles/2015/08/05/new-ebola-cases-in-single-digits-for-2nd-week-says-who" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-08-05T18:17:08Z</updated>
    <published>2015-08-05T18:17:08Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;DAKAR, Senegal (AP) - New Ebola cases were in the single digits another week, the World Health Organization said Wednesday, showing that contact tracing efforts are yielding results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week, Sierra Leone has reported two new cases, both relatives of a man who died from Ebola in Tonkolili, an area that hadn't seen the deadly virus in months.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-08-05T18:17:08Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Officials: Alabama home quarantined over possible Ebola case</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.miamiherald.com/living/health-fitness/article30019245.html%23storylink=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-08-05T13:54:09Z</updated>
    <published>2015-08-05T13:54:09Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Officials say a quarantine is in place at a Birmingham home because of a possible Ebola case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Khan says the patient recently traveled to a country with Ebola cases, but he didn't identify the country or name the patient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Khan says the patient didn't have direct contact with anyone known to have Ebola and is considered "low risk" for the disease.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-08-05T13:54:09Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>New Ebola infections raise concerns in Sierra Leone</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.sfgate.com/world/article/New-Ebola-infections-raise-concerns-in-Sierra-6422022.php" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-08-03T19:07:18Z</updated>
    <published>2015-08-03T19:07:18Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The concerns come as the director of the U.S. Center for Disease Control and Prevention, Dr. Tom Frieden, is in Sierra Leone to observe the impact of the Ebola outbreak and to assess steps needed to get the country to zero cases.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-08-03T19:07:18Z</dc:date>
    <media:content url="http://ww3.hdnux.com/photos/40/04/31/8406638/3/920x920.jpg" />
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>CDC head says Sierra Leone in strong place with Ebola</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.chron.com/news/medical/article/Head-of-CDC-in-Sierra-Leone-as-concerns-grow-from-6421234.php" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-08-03T18:25:24Z</updated>
    <published>2015-08-03T18:25:24Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The victim contracted the disease in the capital, traveled to his home village, and was treated for a fever at the local hospital but authorities didn't call the Ebola emergency number.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-08-03T18:25:24Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>CDC head says Sierra Leone in strong place with Ebola</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.daytondailynews.com/ap/ap/international/head-of-cdc-in-sierra-leone-as-concerns-grow-from-/nnByq/" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-08-03T18:25:24Z</updated>
    <published>2015-08-03T18:25:24Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Two new cases of Ebola surfaced in Sierra Leone's Northern Tonkolili District after a man died last week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The district had not had a single case of Ebola in five months.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-08-03T18:25:24Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Tekmira suspends work on Ebola drug, will change name</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.nzherald.co.nz/business/news/article.cfm?c_id=3&amp;amp;objectid=11484323&amp;amp;ref=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-20T20:25:17Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-20T20:25:17Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) " One of the companies that had been studying a potential treatment for the Ebola virus said Monday it will suspend its research on Ebola drugs and change its name.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tekmira Pharmaceuticals Corp. said last month that an experimental Ebola treatment that it was developing would probably fail in a clinical trial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tekmira's experimental drugs were used in at least one patient in 2014 as an Ebola epidemic spread through several West African nations and the search for more effective treatments kicked into high gear.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-20T20:25:17Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Tekmira suspends work on Ebola drug, will change name</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://www.nzherald.co.nz/world/news/article.cfm?c_id=2&amp;amp;objectid=11484323&amp;amp;ref=rss" />
    <author>
      <name />
    </author>
    <updated>2015-07-20T20:25:17Z</updated>
    <published>2015-07-20T20:25:17Z</published>
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Tekmira said it will suspend work on its drug TKM-Ebola and is re-evaluating its development contract with the U.S. Department of Defense.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The company said in June that a related drug, TKM-Ebola-Guinea, would probably fail in a mid-stage clinical trial.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    <dc:date>2015-07-20T20:25:17Z</dc:date>
  </entry>
</feed>
